we were good we
we were good we
were kind of Dream that can't be so we
were kind of Dream that can't be so we
were right until we W built a Home and watched it
were right till we W built a Home and
I didn't Leave i didn't c
I didn't Leave i
but remember
didn't c but
some
remember some
flowers my
flowers my
name Talk Myself for
name Talk Myself for
hours see you [Music
hours see you
]
[Música]
don't k k me p k
don't k k me
m
p k m
P
P
[Music]
[Música]
And I
And I
can
can
[Music]
[Música]
i
i
su
su
[Music]
[Música]
he
he
H
H
[Music] project
[Música]
Pro
Pro
sm
sm
MC
MC
Don't
Don't
maha
maha
po
po
night
night
[Music] [
[Música]
up swe
up swe
like K is in Jungle K is in Jungle K is
like K is in Jungle K is in Jungle K is
in  Jungle
in Jungle
list K is in The Jungle K is in The
list K is in The Jungle K is in The
Jungle K is  in The Jungle
Jungle K is in The Jungle
[Music]
[Música]
jung jung
jung
j k in jung K in Jungle K in
j k in jung K in Jungle K in
Jungle
Jungle
K is in The Jungle K is in
K is in The Jungle K is in
Jungle is in a Jungle is in jung K is in
Jungle is in a Jungle is in jung K is in
a [Music
a
]
[Música]
Jungle K is in a
Jungle K is in a
jun
jun
[Music]
[Música]
he
he
[Applause] [
[Aplausos]
Music]
[Música]
a
a
[Applause]
[Aplausos]
Oh
Oh
[Music]
[Música]
She got a Smile that  it seems to meind
She got a Smile that it seems to meind
me
me
of m was as the Bright Blue  my you
of
be When I need to
my you be When I need to
the Don't Let Me Let me let me down let
the Don't Let Me Let me let me
me  down let me
down let me down let me
[Music]
[Música]
down Don't let me
down Don't let me
down
down
[Music]
[Música]
Down
Down
Don't let me down down [
Don't let me down down
Music]
[Música]
down Don't let me down Don't let me down down [
down Don't let me down Don't let me down
down I lose my
down I los My
[Applause]
[Aplausos]
[Music]
[Música]
Mind need you I need you I need you
Mind need you I need you I need you
right now yeah I need you right now so
right now yeah I need you right now so
Don't Let Me Don't Let Me Don't let me
Don't Let Me Don't Let Me Don't let me
down I think I'm losing my mind now it's in
down I think I'm losing My Mind Now It's
my head dar hope that you be here
In My Head dar hope that you be here
when I need you the most so Don't Let Me Don't Let Me Don't let me down Don't let me down
When I need you the most so Don't Let Me
[Music]
[Música]
mir
mir
Well good night How are my
Bueno buenas noches Cómo está mi
people how is my Peña How is my
gente cómo está mi Peña Cómo está mi
Peña my goodness wait a moment because I just got
Peña madre mía un momento porque me
off I just went out to go down
acabo de bajar acabo de salir a bajar
dog my goodness I just went out to go down
perro madre mía acabo de salir a bajar
dog and I saw my face in the
perro y me he visto la cara en el
elevator and wow and
ascensor y vaya tela y vaya
wow I just
tela
saw it or I mean I just  I've
me acabo de verla o sea me acabo me
been seeing more or less fine all afternoon
llevaba viendo toda la tarde más o menos
but when I came down when I
bien pero cuando he bajado cuando he
came down now when I went to get the dog
bajado ahora que he ido a bajar el perro
and I saw myself in the
y me he visto en el espejo del
elevator mirror oh my goodness oh my goodness you can't
ascensor madre mía madre mía no podéis
imagine how I look
hacer una idea de la pinta que
you can't imagine how I look let's see I'm
llevo no os podéis hacer una idea de la
going to see if this
pinta que llevo a ver voy a ver si esto
the cameras more or less match with the
las cámaras más o menos coinciden con el
crab it's going to be to match the
cangrejo va a estar para cuadrar las
cameras with the crab no let's see Ugh it's going to be it's going to be
cámaras con el cangrejo no a ver Uf va a
complicated
estar va a estar complicado
eh I think the banana I wanted to
eh yo creo que el plátano he querido
make the crab joke but I
hacer la gracia del cangrejo pero yo
think the banana is better no no come on here
creo que el plátano es mejor no no venga
the crab come on come on the
va el cangrejo venga va va el
crab yes go I put the crab here in
cangrejo sí va pongo el cangrejo aquí en
the gentlemen go okay come here the
la señoreros va está bien venga aquí el
crab
cangrejo
and here how is this here let's see the
y aquí cómo está esto aquí a ver la
camera either let's see I can't overdo it either I can't
cámara tampoco a ver tampoco puedo
stay
abusar tampoco puedo estar mucho rato
here for too long either I can't stay here for too long either Let's
Aquí tampoco puedo estar yo mucho rato
see There's the crab either I can't stay
Aquí a ver Ahí está el cangr Tampoco
here for too long either I'm going to be
tampoco puedo estar mucho rato Aquí voy
a challenge I'm going to be commenting on
a estar un rete voy a estar comentando
some
algunos
topics but don't think I can't overdo it I have my
temas pero tampoco creáis que puedo
head swollen
abusar tengo tengo la cabeza hinchad
abyss the return of the banana man
sima el retorno del plátano hombre a mí
the banana seems to me Good  this is
el plátano me parece Bueno este está
fun too no no your neck will hurt your neck
divertido también no no te dolerá el
Why is your neck
qué el cuello Por
Why no no no my head has been hurting
qué no no no me ha estado doliendo la
Yesterday I was really bad eh Yesterday I
cabeza Ayer estuve malísimo eh Ayer
was bad bad bad bad I wanna feel
estuve malo malo malo malo quio sentir
your body Hey here Fran is on
tu cuerpo Oye que está Fran está en
live right now
directo ahora
yesterday I was really bad yesterday I was
mismo ayer estuve muy mal ayer estuve
really
muy
sick Yesterday when I came out of the operating room I
malito Ayer cuando salí del quirófano
was good [ __ ] great I mean
estaba bueno bien de [__] madre digo
[ __ ] I didn't understand anything
[__] no me he enterado de nada
perfect but the moment I ate in
perfecto pero en el momento que comí por
the afternoon the effects of
la tarde se me pasó los efectos de la de
the anesthesia and everything else wore off phew really really
la anestesia y demás
bad but now now
puf malísimo malísimo pero ahora ahora
the truth is oh
la verdad es
my god if you saw my face now
que madre mía si me vies la cara ahora
the truth is that now I'm fine let's
la verdad es que ahora estoy
see one thing Now I'm fine the
bien a ver una cosa Ahora estoy bien la
truth is that now I don't feel
verdad es que ahora no me encuentro
bad but oh well I just took the
mal pero bueno Me acabo de tomar la
medication right now at the bus stop if I
medicación ahora mismo en la parada si
'm going to be I'm going to be quiet
voy a est voy a estar tranquilito
commenting on the gossip recording a couple of
comentando el chisme grabando un par de
extracts and everything if I see that I
extractos y demás si veo que me
feel bad or whatever then I'm going I would
encuentro mal o lo que sea pues me voy
like to record one I would like to record
me gustaría grabar un me gustaría grabar
both I didn't do it the
los dos No hiciero la
truth But what happened to you pain Yes yes a lot a
verdad Pero qué te pasó dolor Sí sí
lot  Well, it's very swollen, I have it, I have it
mucho mucho Bueno hinchazón muchísimo
swollen right now, let's say
Tengo tengo hinchado ahora mismo vamos
the face that I have right
la cara que tengo ahora mismo la del
now, the crab's filter, the crab's filter, I think it's a thousand times better, I mean, I have it, I have super swollen, my head started looking like a setangana between the baldness that they did to me and the swollen head, I started looking like a setangana then I went to the series and I Juan and what's happening now is that I can't describe it to you, I
y lo de ahora es que no os lo puedo
mean, what's happening now is
describir o sea lo de ahora es de
sudden But well, when I was
repente Pero bueno cuando estaba en
live with Marina I didn't notice
directo con Marina yo no me he notado
anything but since I went down to take the
nada pero como he bajado a bajar al
dog for a
perro un
second I got a fever yesterday, yes, Jack Well,
segundo me dio fiebre ayer sí Jack Pues
I have like the whole east side above my
tengo como todo el lado este de arriba
eyes and around the eyes and
de los ojos y alrededor de los ojos y de
the 100 around here on the side is swollen swollen swollen
la 100 por aquí al lado inflado inflado
but oh well, they told me that it was
inflado pero bueno Me avisaron que era
normal, eh, they told me that I might even have
normal eh Me avisaron que se me incluso
branches coming out in my eyes, don't
salir de rames en los ojos que no me
panic, go on family, it will be a few days from
asuste va familia serán unos días de
now until next week I'm already
aquí a la semana que viene ya estoy
visible, I'm sure the time when my
visible seguro el tiempo que que ya
hair can grow a little bit, what
pueda crecer un poquito el pelo de lo de
they cut is that they
lo que me han cortado es que me han
shaved half of my head
Rapado tío la mitad de la cabeza para
down  They shaved me so much I didn't believe they were
abajo me han Rapado que yo no creía que
going to shave that
me iban a rapar
much I didn't believe they were going to shave that
tanto yo no creía que me iban a rapar
much The truth is I refused to
tanto La verdad me me he negado a
shave it
raparme
and I told him to shave my j's and
y le dije que me rapara los j y los
just right it was the whole part the
justito ha sido toda la parte
whole bottom part the whole
de toda la parte de abajo toda la parte
bottom part but
de abajo pero
well no Karime nothing no you don't understand
bueno no Karime nada no no te enteras de
anything the truth I mean during
nada la verdad O sea que durante durante
the operation you prick them you understand
la operación los pinchas yos te entera
a little bit of the pricks from the
un poquito í de los pinchaso de la
anesthesia but nothing nothing that you can't
anestesia pero nada nada que no se pueda
stand for a second Pin Pin Pin the
soportar un segundo Pin Pin Pin se te
whole area quickly goes numb and both
duerme rápidamente toda la zona y tanto
the hour and a half that they are removing the
la hora y media que están quitándote la
donor part and then the one they put in there
parte donante como luego la que te ponen
is a break
hay un descanso
and then 3 hours putting hair on you 3 hours
y luego 3 horas poniéndote pelo 3 horas
5000 hairs they put on me eh I don't know if they
5000 pelos me han puesto eh No sé si
showed the images someday eh I don't
enseñaron las imágenes algún día eh No
know if I will show you the images but just
sé si enseñaros las imágenes pero solo
so you can see eh all the hair that I was missing
para que veáis eh todo lo que me faltaba
eh in the entrances I
de pelo eh en las entrada o
mean I don't know how Let's see Look I'm going to get
sea no sé cómo A ver Mira voy a [__] el
Paint and I'm going to describe it to you with
Paint y os lo voy a describir con el
Paint I mean there were people who said  that I did
Paint O sea que había gente que decía
n't need it but I did
que no me hacía falta pero si hacía
need it look it was more or less let's see it was more
falta mira era más o menos a ver era más
or less let's imagine that it's on my
o menos imaginemos que está en mi
head okay let's imagine that it's on my
cabeza vale imaginemos que está en mi
head
cabeza
okay And over here I had my a it can't get
vale Y yo por aquí pues tenía mi a no se
any thicker I combed my hair
puede poner más grueso yo me peinaba
well here not my quiffs and
bien aquí no mis tupés y
everything else good quiff also the truth is that I
demás buen tupé además la verdad que me
combed my hair very well Let's have it I'm not
peinaba muy bien Vamos lo tengo no me lo
going to cut it okay
voy a cortar vale
but
pero
here look I'm going to paint it with red everything
aquí mira lo voy a pintar con rojo todo
that they've put on me okay all this
lo que me han puesto vale todo
this one on this side was tremendous
esto este la de este lado era tremenda O
I mean the one on this side went in Even a little bit in here Okay and outside it starts a little bit further down the line You know that it had gone up on me over
Sabes que se me había subido con el paso
the years I mean if I had taken it if I had left it if I had
de los años o sea si yo me lo lleo si yo
left it would have
dejar si me lo llego a dejar se me
turned the quiff into an island on an
convierte lo del tupé En una isla en una
island just the quiff I mean all this
isla solamente el tupé o sea todo esto
all this the two entrances and this one
todo esto las dos entradas y esta sobre
especially this one went in when I
todo esta se me metía para dentro cuando
saw it on camera it turned me pitch black
me la veo en cámara me ponía negrísimo
So nothing eh
Así que nada
Well at first you'll see me as
eh Bueno al principio me veréis como
if nothing had happened next week  that's coming
como si nada la semana que viene ya
when it's visible that I'll fix my
cuando esté visible que me arregle un
hair a little bit no no no no no tesa
poquito el pel no no no no no tesa
exaggerated no Well tesa have you seen the
exagerado no Bueno tesa tú has visto la
photo that I sent you, I mean to you
foto que a ti te las he mandado o sea te
if it's 5000 hair, I mean the two
la si es que son 5000 pelo o sea las dos
entrances and this one here is getting in the way eh
entradas y esta de aquí se mete tela eh
at the beginning when you see me when you
al principio cuando me veáis cuando me
see me when it's visible again I think that
veáis cuando vuelva a ser visible yo
by I think that by
creo que para yo creo que para la semana
next week I'm visible the truth is nothing
que viene Estoy visible la verdad nada
more than nothing more than the
más que nada más que se me baje el
swelling goes down I can wash my hair
hinchazón me pueda lavar la cabeza
in 4 days that I wash my hair a little bit I
dentro de 4 días que me lave un poquito
can comb it a little bit
la cabeza me pueda peinar un poquillo
forward like this with my hands
para adelante así con las manos
and and let the hair on the sides grow a little bit
y y me crezca un poquito lo de los lados
I think that by next week it wo
que yo creo que para la semana que viene
n't be so shaved I don't know what you know I
ya no estará tan Rapado no sé que sabes
mean let's see I won't be well well well
o sea a ver no estaré bien bien bien
But I will be a little more visible you guys
Pero estaré un poco más visible ustedes
in what the implant is you're not going to
en lo que es el implante no lo Vais a
notice until the part
notar hasta que no ya crezca la parte
that they put in grows out Of
que me han puesto
course but well these are things The truth is
Claro pero bueno son cosas La verdad a
I don't mind saying the challenges that
mí no me importa decir los retos que que
I do the
yo me hago la
truth is it takes a month  the scab falls off
verdad un mes tarda en caerse la costra
Javi well each person is a world eh
Javi bueno cada persona es un mundo eh
each person is a world For example
cada persona es un mundo Yo por ejemplo
the whole back part the
la toda la parte de atrás la parte
donor part that yesterday was criminal no yesterday
donante que ayer estaba criminal no ayer
the whole donor part the whole
toda la parte donante estaba toda la
head was with red dots no today for
cabeza con puntos rojos no hoy ya por
example I have it as if nothing eh
ejemplo lo tengo como como si nada eh
today I have it as if
hoy ya lo tengo como si
nothing this happens this happens very quickly a
nada esto pasa esto pasa rapidísimo una
week or two It's over it's over it takes
semana o dos Ya está ya
time to grow man of course
pasó tarda en crecer hombre claro date
realize that it starts as if it starts from
cuenta que empieza como si empieza de
scratch I think that until at least
cero yo creo que hasta por lo menos
within the result Great Great Great Great Great
dentro el resultado Guay Guay Guay Guay
I think that for winter well
yo creo que para invierno
to sleep peacefully I try to
pues para dormir tranquilamente intento
get into positions so that the
ponerme de posturas que no me toque la
part where they put me doesn't touch and that's it
parte donde me han puesto y ya
nothing happens nothing happens nothing happens but let's
nada no pasa nada no pasa nada pero a
see the truth is that I think I'm glad I did it
ver yo la verdad que creo que me alegro
eh where did you do it Rocio Rocio
eh dónde te lo has hecho Rocío Rocío
Vazquez I always get it done at Rocio
Vázquez Yo siempre me hago en Rocío
Vazquez in my trusted clinic
Vázquez en mi clínica de confianza
eh except for the botox that I got done in
eh menos lo del botox que me lo hice en
a center that I'm not going to mention and I didn't
un centro que no voy a mencionar y no me
like it you have to use minoxidil HM I
gustó te tienes que echar minoxidil HM
don't know I have a treatment that I have
No lo sé tengo un tratamiento que tengo
to do during  a few years a
que hacer durante unos años un
treatment that is already for the rest
tratamiento que es ya para que al resto
of my head the rest of the hair so that it does not
de mi cabeza al resto de pelo porque no
fall out to give it a certain density and a
se caiga que le dé cierta densidad y
certain quality but it is very cool very
cierta calidad pero es muy Guay muy
cool yes Karime I mean I
Guay sí Karime o sea yo lo del pelo lo
was clear about the hair eh I mean I would go bald and
tenía claro eh o sea yo quedarme calvo y
all that no no Why not that that I
demás no no Por qué no eso eso yo
always in life always in life I have
siempre en la vida siempre en la vida he
had the doubt I would go bald but no
tenido la duda me quedaría calvo pero no
no I was following the same path as my father
no llevaba el mismo camino que mi padre
the same the same
el mismo igual el mismo
and now you are a subscriber of XD of what
y ahora eres un suscriptor de XD de qué
of utbh Ah well
de utbh Ah pues
look precisely the first
mira precisamente precisamente el primer
video that we are going to see now is from tvh
vídeo que vamos a ver ahora es de tvh
HM we are going to react to this part of the
HM vamos a reaccionar a esta parte de la
interview that of the talk that he had
entrevista que de la charla que él tuvo
with Fran in which he gives traya to ibai to
con Fran en la que le da traya a ibai a
Ricky edie to the girlfriend and all these people I
Ricky edie a la novia y toda esta gente
saw a click that he put on Twitter and I
vi un click que él puso en Twitter y
say Wow this is gold for me to
digo Wow esto es oro para mí para para
react to the live we are
reaccionar lo en directo
not going to see it
no vamos a verlo
family the Ricky edit from the other day
familia lo de Ricky edit del otro día
with the girlfriend they told me You are
con la novia me decían Es que le estás
screwing the girl I don't know
jodiendo a la chica me venían no sé
how many came to say You are a son of a [ __ ] that does
cuántas a decir Eres un hijo de [__] que
not  I know what we're going to see if the girl has been
no sé qué vamos a ver si a la chica le
raped Like Ricky said Go to a
han violado Como dijo Ricky Vete a una
[ __ ] police station Don't do a Stream
[__] comisaría No te hagas un Stream
to say that you've been raped Ugh look at
para decir que te han violado Uf mira lo
Ricky's thing As for Ricky's girlfriend, I do
de la Ricky Lo de la novia de Ricky yo
n't think we're going to go into much
creo que ya tampoco vamos a entrar mucho
more either, we're not going to give it much more force,
más no le vamos a dar mucha más fuerta
okay, let her congratulate her ex on her
vale que felicite a su ex por su
birthday, what about another person while you
cumple qu pi otra persona mientras lo
're
estáis
doing it, let her chat with a person she
haciendo que chatee con una persona que
met through a
conoció a través de una aplicación de
dating app like
citas como viene a ser
Tinder and last but not least, let her delete messages from
tinder y última que borre mensajes de
a conversation so you don't
una conversación para que tú no los
see them I think what was written up here
veas creo que lo que ponía aquí arriba
were horns not horns something like that I don't
eran cuernos no cuernos algo así no me
remember it's that they sent me this click
acuerdo es que me mandaron este click
on Instagram and well it caught my
por Instagram y bueno me llamó la
attention, honestly, truth be told, at least
atención la verdad verdad cuanto mínimo
but as for this thing with Ricky and Lali, I
pero ya lo de lo de esto de Ricky y Lali
don't think it has more I'm going to give you
tampoco creo que tenga más os voy a dar
a little exclusive on the news
una pequeña exclusiva en el noticiero
when I can record it, hopefully I
cuando lo pueda grabar que ojalá lo
can record it tonight so that the
pueda grabar esta noche para que ya el
news has life Today again,
noticiero tenga vida Hoy de nuevo
eh, if I don't feel too bad, okay, what I'm
eh si no me encuentro muy mal vale lo
going to do is not be here for too long
que voy a hacer es no estar mucho tiempo
here at the canijo I'll do an hour hour and a
aquí en el canijo haré una hora hora y
half I'll try I'll try to make it an
media intentaré intentaré que sea una
hour and a half live so that it
hora hora y media de directo para que me
also gives me the life and the strength to be able
dé también la vida y la fuerza para
to record a newscast I don't know if I'll be
llegar a grabar un noticiero no sé si ya
able to record the lollipop but at
podré grabar de la piruleta pero por lo
least I'll have enough time to record a newscast
menos que me dé para grabar un noticiero
with Javi Oliveira Because I have to
de Javi oliveira Porque os tengo que
show you some exclusive images
Mostrar unas imágenes en exclusiva
beautiful beautiful beautiful beautiful you'll
guapas guapas guapas guapas ya las
see them okay But well it doesn't have
veréis vale Pero bueno tampoco tiene
much more eh I mean I think they've broken up
mucho más eh o sea yo creo que han roto
more than broken up and that and Ricky will start
más que roto y que y que Ricky irá
opening his eyes I hope I'm not wrong
abriendo los ojos espero no equivocarme
but I think Ricky is going to start opening his
pero creo que Ricky va a ir abriendo los
eyes and as he starts opening his
ojos y conforme vaya abriendo los
eyes he'll be more sensible with his
ojos será más Sensato con su sus
movements and with his behavior I
movimientos y con sus comportamientos
think eh I mean you can't go on a
creo eh o sea tú no puedes salir en un
Stream saying I've been raped and since
Stream diciendo me han violado y como no
nothing can be done with justice which
se puede hacer nada con la justicia que
nothing can be done with justice
no se puede hacer nada con la justicia
in Spain if you arrive and they say that you've been
en España si llegas y dicen que te han
raped and you're a famous streamer girlfriend
violado y eres una streamer famosa novia
of a famous streamer [ __ ] You just have to
de un streamer famoso [__] Solo tienes
say Irene in a tweet Irene I've been
que decir Irene en un twet Irene me han
raped Ricky edit says Irene  they've
violado Ricky edit pone Irene me han
raped me, damn the geos come from wherever
violado [__] llegan los geos donde
here
sea aquí
I
yo
believe here I believe that since Ricky is a
creo aquí yo creo que como Ricky es una
person who is not very in line with the ideals
persona que no es muy afín a los ideales
of Irene Montero and this Peña wouldn't get
de Irene Montero y esta Peña no se
as involved as maybe if she
mojaría tanto como a lo mejor si de
suddenly came out
repente saliera
imagine I don't want to put any it
imagínate Es que no quiero poner ningún
would be in bad taste to put another name no
sería de mal gusto poner otro nombre no
but yes some some twitterer that was in
pero sí algún alguna tuitera que fuese a
line with the ideals of Irene Montero
fin a las ideales de de Irene Montero
but what happens is that I In my opinion In my
pero qué pasa que yo A mi parecer A mi
opinion we love you Red heart crab
parecer te queremos Cangrejito corazón
I'm glad you're better I'm glad to
rojo me alegra que estés mejor Me alegra
hear you Maribel Thank you very much I
escucharte Maribel Muchísimas gracias
hope you appreciated the effort I'm
Espero que valoré el esfuerzo que estoy
making okay I'm still kind of sick
haciendo vale que estoy medio malus
but I'm here because I missed you a
todavía pero estoy aquí porque os echaba
lot yesterday In my opinion It
mucho de menos ayer A mi parecer Me
seems to me that as you say they've made a
parece que se ha montado como dices tú
tremendous movie and they've trivialized
tremenda película y han banalizado con
something that can't be trivialized
una cosa que no se puede banalizar
so I do want here here yes I am
entonces yo sí que quiero aquí aquí sí
interested and in fact I got in
que me interesa y de hecho yo me puse en
touch with the Ministry eh I am
contacto con el Ministerio eh A mí sí me
interested in this being resolved and in finding
interesa que se resuelva eso y que se
out who the sexual one is that is out
sepa quién es el de sexual que está por
there that raped the girlfriend  from Ricky edit
ahí que violó a la novia de Ricky edit
I want to know who that [ __ ]
Yo quiero saber quién es ese [__]
Predator is and that they put him in jail.
Depredador y que lo metan en la cárcel
I do want to know because he raped
yo sí quiero saberlo porque ha violado a
Ricky's girlfriend. Now, whatever it is, it's a
la novia de Ricky elli ahora como sea
lie. I curse the [ __ ] who gave birth to them
mentira me cago en la [__] que los parí
both. But of course you can't say that
a los dos pero claro no puedes decir eso
because those things can't be
porque es que de esas cosas no se pueden
said. But why not, why not?
decir pero por qué no pero por qué no
Where is the [ __ ] freedom? I say that they
Dónde está la [__] libertad yo digo que
raped her, [ __ ]. Apart from that, he's not
la han violado [__] aparte no te está
telling you bad, he's telling you that he
diciendo malo te está diciendo que
wants that if there is a rapist, a
quiere que si hay un violador un
Predator who is going to be one again.
Depredador que lo va a volver a
Hello to the crab, where did you leave the
ser Hola a cangrejo donde dejaste al
brat? Hehe and hey, grandpa, I know this
canijo Jeje y Oye abuelo sé que esto te
takes you by surprise, but do you think you could
toma de sorpresa pero crees que podrías
address the issue of a tiktoker
tratar el tema de una tiktoker que se
named albertina zcal, she is going through a
llama albertina zcal le está pasando una
very unfortunate funa and it would be good to
funa muy desafortunada y sería bueno
unfuna that by tomorrow, okay, go
desfunado a eso ya para mañana vale ira
for that one, we have to go after the son of a [ __ ]
por ese hay que ir a por el hijo [__]
who raped her, of course, I mean, he's not
que la ha violado claro o sea no está
saying anything bad, he's telling you that he has to be
diciendo nada malo te está diciendo que
located and we have to make him
hay que localizarlo y hay que hacerle
pay, we have to make him pay. Hey, the
pagar hay que hacerle pagar Oye el
problem here is that  suddenly
problema aquí está en que de repente
they the others can prove that
ellos los otros puedan demostrar que
Lali is lying okay like the
Lali está mintiendo vale como la
information that came to me to me
información que a mí me llegó a mí me
very, very reliable information came
llegó una información muy pero que muy
to me very, very reliable information
fiable a mí me llegó una información muy
very, very reliable that the
fiable muy pero que muy fiable de
others if Ali decides to
que los otros si al Ali se le ocurre
report or expose the kid they have
denunciar o exponer al chaval tienen de
everything to go against her conversations
todo para ir contra ella conversaciones
audios and everything
audios y de todo
eh but as I say that's not that she's not
eh pero como digo eso no es que no está
mentally prepared [ __ ] and she's
preparada mentalmente [__] y está
prepared for a [ __ ] month or I don't
preparada para durante un [__] mes o no
know how many streams or videos saying I've
sé cuántos streams o vídeos diciendo me
been raped It's that she's raped
han violado Es que la han violado decía
Ricky trunk said that your girlfriend has been raped
Ricky tronco que han violado a tu novia
and you're not calling Montero air you
y no estás llamando a aire de Montero tú
or I mean let's get up Rome with Santiago
o sea vamos yo levanto Roma con Santiago
look with lawyers and they told me that if
fíjate con abogados y me dijeron que si
the affected person does not report they do not
la persona afectada no denuncia no
make a statement regardless of whether they
presta declaración independientemente de
go to whatever at the moment in which
que vayaa lo que sea en el momento en el
the other person directly you can make
que la otra persona directo puedes hacer
all the show you want okay I here
todo el show que quieras vale Yo aquí
with you I can tell you but if later
contigo puedo decirte pero si yo luego
a police officer comes and in his report and
viene un policía y en su atestado y
when he's I don't say anything nor do I say
cuando me está Yo no digo nada ni digo
that I have not consented nor do I repeat the same thing
que no he consentido ni repito lo mismo
that I've been telling you here this  it's
que te estado contando aquí esto no vale
worthless okay okay But then you tell
nada vale vale Pero entonces tú dime a
me You tell me if you say in a Stream
mí Tú dime a mí si tú en un Stream dices
that you've been raped okay you Tomorrow you come
que te han violado vale tú Mañana llegas
and say [ __ ] a guy grabbed me on the
y dices [__] me cogió un tío por la
street he [ __ ] me he raped me eh but I'm
calle me enculó me violó eh pero me da
ashamed to say it because nothing's going to happen
vergüenza decirlo porque no va a pasar
and the minister of equality comes to you
nada y te viene el minister misio de
the prosecutor's office says hey we're
igualdad la fiscalía te dice Oye te
going to help you You don't
vamos a ayudar No
report why don't you report do you
denuncias por qué no denuncias te
remember the ass hoax yes I remember
acuerdas del bulo del culo sí recuerdo
clearly it was a tremendous event that's how
claro fue tremendo evento así son las
things are that's how things are these days that it
cosas así son las cosas estos días que
's very easy to say I've been raped it's very
es muy fácil decir me han violado es muy
easy to say I've been abused and maybe it
fácil decir me han abusado y que a lo
's true But what I don't
mejor es verdad Pero yo lo que no
understand is that if you've been abused And you
entiendo es que si te han abusado Y
're mentally so screwed and so
estás mentalmente tan jodida y tan
screwed How the [ __ ] do you have the balls to
[__] Cómo [__] tien los hos de
go on a Stream to say that you've been
salir en un Stream a decir que te han
raped and to say that
violado y a decir es que han violado a
my girlfriend has been raped trunk for Mental Health
mi novia tronco por la Salud Mental
Shut up take care of her and let her take care of herself there are
Cállate cuídala y que se cuide yo hay
things that I don't understand I understand
cosas que no entiendo yo lo entiendo
perfectly let's see here flan here flan flan
perfectamente a ver aquí flan aquí flan
flan  I'm going to eat egg flan.
flan flan flan de huevo me voy a comer
Today to rest here Fran is
Yo hoy para descansar aquí Fran está
being completely ironic I mean we all
siendo irónico completamente o sea todos
understand the same thing absolutely everyone who
entendemos lo mismo absolutamente todos
has two brain cells and knows how to add
que tenga dos neuronas y que sepan sumar
understands the same thing I mean this girl has been
entienden lo mismo o sea esta chica le
caught cheating on her
han pillado poniéndole los cuernos al
boyfriend and and and she's grabbed onto the idea that it's
novios y y y se ha agarrado a que es un
abuse That's it, nothing's happening, it's not the
abuso Ya está no pasa nada no es la
first eh It's not the first case that I know of
primera eh No es el primer caso que sé
I know more cases some that I can
conozco más casos algunos que los puedo
tell you about and another one well No none I can
contar y otro bueno No ninguno lo puedo
tell you the truth unless they do
contar la verdad a no s que me hagan
something to me let's see I think that there they
algo a mí a ver yo creo que ahí
made a I think that Ricky himself
cometieron yo creo que el propio Ricky
has recognized that they made mistakes
lo ha reconocido que cometieron errores
by exposing it publicly at first
al exponerlo públicamente en un primer
and then there it seems to me that there has
momento y luego ya ahí me parece que ha
been a domino effect that has led to
habido un efecto dominó que ha llevado a
Well, to these kinds of you know I'm going to
Pues a estas especies de sabes Voy a
bare my soul here in front of
desnudar mi alma aquí delante de todo el
everyone for 50 minutes No but [ __ ] you
mundo durante 50 minutos No pero [__] tú
can't say No it's that she's going to commit
no puedes decir No es que se va a
suicide I mean we're dealing with the issue of
suicidar o sea estamos con el tema de la
Mental Health we're dealing with the issue of I
Salud Mental estamos con el tema de o
mean Sorry to tell you
sea Perdona que te diga
don't tell me It's that you know what
a mí no me digas Es que sabes lo que
happens it turns out that now  everything is
pasa que resulta que ahora todo es abuso
sexual abuse everything is Mental Health everything is
sexual todo es Salud Mental todo es un
[ __ ] victimhood And this is the [ __ ]
[__] victimismo Y esta es la [__]
society Yeah so the third time you
sociedad Sí entonces a la tercera vez
say I've been abused but I don't
que ya digas me han abusado pero no
report it you say it's that I was in the
denuncio dices es que estaba en las
clubs and there's a sign behind me that
discotecas y tiene un cartel detras que
says Fame don't [ __ ] with me I mean there comes
dice Fame no me jodas o sea es que llega
a time when I understand that there are
un momento en el cual yo entiendo que
a lot of women who abuse them, who
hay un montón de mujeres que las abusan
use them, who treat them like
que las usan que que las tratan como la
[ __ ] but [ __ ] when you're a streamer you
[__] pero [__] cuando eres un streamer
're there to set an
estás para dar
example you're in front of the public and you
ejemplo estás de cara al público y no
can't trivialize something and for me it becomes
puedes banalizar algo y para mí se
trivialized the moment you do a
banaliza en el momento que tú haces un
Stream to say I've been raped How
Stream para decir me han violado Cómo
can you say he's raped and stay
puedes decir le han violado y quedarte
so Pancho it's not that look I thought he had cheated on
tan Pancho no es que fíjate yo creí que
me but it
me había puesto los cuernos pero es que
was a rape dude but what the [ __ ] is
fue una violación troncón pero qu [__]
wrong with you This then now I'm
cabeza te cabe Esto entonces ahora Estoy
calmer because now we're
más tranquilo porque ahora ya somos
boyfriend and girlfriend again I don't
novios otra vez yo que es que no lo
understand it my head is going that maybe
entiendo se me va la cabeza que a lo
I'm the one in the wrong for sure because
mejor yo soy el equivocado seguro porque
I'm neither art nor part But you know what
no soy ni arte ni parte Pero sabes lo
happens I have children I have children and
que pasa Yo tengo hijos yo tengo hijos y
my children I hope they don't do anything wrong
mis hijos Espero que no hagan nada malo
in their lives but I hope that
en su vida pero espero que tampoco
no [ __ ] comes along to
aparezca ninguna hija de la gran [__] a
screw up their lives and right now
joderle la vida y en estos momentos
thanks to things
gracias a cosas
like this people have doubts I have doubts
así la gente tiene dudas yo tengo dudas
because it turns out there is the law of yes is yes no is no this is
porque resulta que está la ley del sí es
no this is the other from here to
sí del no es no de esto de lo otro de
there there are so many
para aquí de para allá hay tantos
rights there are so many friend I believe you I don't
derechos hay tantos amiga yo te creo no
know what I don't know how much or whatever Look what
sé qué no sé cuánto o sea Mira la que se
has happened over a kiss Well if you come you
ha montado por un beso Pues si tú llegas
are a famous streamer and you say that you have
eres una streamer famosa y dices que te
been raped what do you think they are not going to
han violado tú qu te crees que no te van
help you don't [ __ ] with me I know that it is a
a ayudar no me jodas sé que es un tema
very difficult subject that should not be talked about
muy [__] que no se debe de hablar
eh boy I want it to be known what
eh chico yo quiero que se sepa qué ha
happened there and I want it to be there is a
pasado ahí y quiero que sea hay un
sexual predator in Madrid or wherever
depredador sexual en Madrid o donde sea
that they catch him Total that's it because what I have
que lo pillen Total ya está porque yo lo
heard a strick is that a
que he escuchado un strick es que a una
girl has been
chica la han
raped and that she is afraid to report it
violado y que tiene miedo de denunciar
because she says that justice is not going to
porque dice que la justicia no va a
work well what [ __ ] a girl is
funcionar pues vaya [__] una chica la
raped and she doesn't believe in justice what
violan y y no cree en la justicia vaya
[ __ ] Well I think we will need
[__] Pues yo creo que necesitaremos
two ministries of equality right now
dos ministerios de igualdad ahora mismo
or  three because it seems that that that that on
o tres porque parece que que que que que
top of that it's not Mental Health
encima es eso no la Salud Mental la
Mental Health what you do is cut off
Salud Mental lo que haces es cortar las
social media and not say anything go to a
redes sociales y no decir nada ir a una
police station or stay at home with your
comisaría o quedarte en tu casa con tu
boyfriend or your family that no that nothing happens no no I didn't
novio o tu familia que no que no pas
cheat on him that I was
nada no no le puse los cuernos que me
raped man I mean where are we that she cheated on her
violaron tronco o sea dónde estamos que
boyfriend that's it she
le ha puesto los cuernos al novio ya
cheated on him and
está que le ha puesto los cuernos y ha
said that that I have children that I
dicho eso que yo tengo hijos que yo
have [ __ ]
tengo [__]
children living in
hijos viviendo en
Spain I
España O
mean what happens if this happens to you because maybe there
sea qué pasa si te toca esto porque es
's a guy right now who's
que a lo mejor hay un chico ahora mismo
scared because he hasn't raped anyone and they're
acojonado porque no ha violado a nadie y
calling him a rapist and he's
le están llamando violador y está
scared he's not scared he's not
acojonado no está acojonado no está
scared I'm getting
acojonado a mí me llegan informaciones
very reliable information very reliable that the guy
muy fiables muy fiables de que el chico
has everything and Lali is not going to come out to
lo tiene todo y Lali no va a salir a
deny it or well not to deny it
desmentir ni a bueno no a desmentir ella
Lali is not going to come out to put or I mean she's never
Lali no va a salir a poner o sea nunca
going to put a face to the guy if you
le va a poner cara al chico si os dais
notice She's never going to put a face to the
cuenta Ella nunca le va a poner cara al
guy or give any
chico ni va ni va a dar ninguna
hints  who she actually belongs to, all she's
indirecta de quién es de hecho todo lo
done is you guys have seen that you
que ha hecho es ustedes habéis visto que
've deleted that Lali has deleted a
habéis borrado que ha borrado Lali un
bunch of tweets,
montón de tweet
sorry, forgive me for speaking worse than
perdon perdonarme que hable peor de
usual, okay, but I'm still feeling the
costumbre vale pero estoy todavía con
effects of the
efectos de la
medication, the anesthesia, anyway, a
medicación las anestesias en fin un
lot of things are still going on in my body, forgive me
montón de cosas todavía en el cuerpo
if I spoke badly,
perdonarme que ya si hablaba mal
forgive me for expressing myself worse in these
perdonarme que me exprese peor en estos
live shows, okay, these
directos vale estos
[Music]
[Música]
days,
días
Lali, a lot of people have realized that she's
Lali mucha gente se ha da cuenta que ha
deleted a lot of tweets and they're wondering
borrado muchos tweet y se preguntan por
why she's deleted the tweets, they thought they were
qué ha borrado tweet se creían que eran
because they left her in a bad light with Dallas, I don't know
por que la dejaban mal con Dallas no sé
what, no, she deleted the twicks so
qué no ella los twicks ha borrado son
people don't find the group
para que no encuentren la gente al grupo
of friends and the boy in question, okay,
de amigos y al chico de marras vale para
so people don't go around spinning and
que la gente no vaya hilando y lo
find him if Ali decides to put a
encuentre si al Ali se le ocurre ponerle
face or a name to the boy or decides to
cara o nombre al chico o se le ocurre
report him, the friends have
denunciar los amigos tienen
conversations with her, I've seen
conversaciones con ella yo he visto
screenshots, okay, they've commented on
pantallazos vale me han comentado
screenshots
pantallazos
because they don't want to pass anything to me until they
porque no me quieren pasar nada hasta
see Lali's movements, but
que no vean los movimientos de Lali pero
screenshots where Lali says that they have to
pantallazos donde Lali dice que tienen
help her lie about lying to
que ayudarla a mentir sobre a mentirle a
Ricky, no
Ricky como
matter what  and I believe them and I believe them I'm
sea y me los creo y me los creo lo
sorry for Lali but I believe them there are
siento por Lali pero me los creo hay
screenshots of Lali I have to
pantallazos de Lali le tengo que
write to her Hey I'm going to write to her tomorrow to
escribir Oye le voy a escribir mañana a
see if she can confirm them because since I
ver si me los confirma porque ya que
wanted me to verify the information with her I'm
quería que verificara con ella la
going to
información Se lo voy a se lo voy a
ask her directly tomorrow Lali there are
preguntar mañana directamente Lali hay
screenshots of you that I've seen
pantallazos tuyos que yo he visto
[Music]
[Música]
that you're asking for and also Lali I
que que tú estás pidiendo y además Lali
can tell you bah but the thing is that I'm not
te puedo decir bah pero es que no te lo
going to tell you because if I tell you you're
voy a decir porque si te lo digo
surely going to know well it's that
seguramente vas a saber bueno es que
Ali surely knows who has those
seguramente Ali sabe quién tiene esos
screenshots It's that why not it's that I
pantallazos Es que para qué no es que os
can even tell you the affectionate nickname that
puedo decir hasta el apodo cariñoso que
those friends have for her
le tienen esos amigos en
on
el en el
WhatsApp It's that you're pulling my
WhatsApp Es que me estáis tirando de la
tongue but the thing is that those messages are
lengua pero es que esos mensajes son
true those messages are true
verdad es que esos mensajes son verdad
Lali and if you don't come out and tell the truth you're going to
Lali y si no sales a decir la verdad vas
look really bad you're still in time she's
a quedar muy mal todavía estás a tiempo
going to
te va a
block you but it's that Ricky really if you
bloquear pero es que Ricky de verdad si
're seeing me you usually see
me estás viendo que tú sueles ver las
things Ricky is
cosas Ricky te está
lying to you he's lying to you Ricky is
mintiendo te está mintiendo Ricky te
lying to you there are conversations and they are
está mintiendo hay conversaciones y son
true eh They are not like the other
verdaderas eh No son como las del otro
day when there were doubts there  conversations
día que había dudas hay conversaciones
where Lali is asking her friends to
donde Lali le está pidiendo a los amigos
lie to you for
que tienen que mentirte por
her don't say anything babe no let's see I just
ella no digas nada churri no a ver yo
do my job I mean more I can't
hago mi trabajo sin más yo o sea más no
eh And already I have already relaxed
puedo eh Y ya he ya me he relajado
because I'm with because I got a
porque estoy con porque me he hecho un
graft because I had to
injerto porque me he tenido que hacer
undergo an operation if not I would
someterme a una operación si no yo estar
still be at my best Hi Javi what happened to you today
a tope todavía Hola Javi qué te paso hoy
you look more handsome than usual Yeah yeah Yes
te ves más guapo de lo normal Ya ya Sí
the truth is that it suits me I'm not going to
la verdad es que me favorece no te voy a
lie to you there isn't an episode like that let's see if it
engañar no hay un episodio así a ver si
is that Of course if you stop to think about what
es que Claro si tú te pones a pensar lo
can happen on a night out where
que puede pasar en una noche de fiesta
people have consumed alcohol where they are
en la que la gente ha consumido alcol en
drunk and all that and they are
la que van borrachos y demás y están
flirting Well in a clumsy way
ligando Pues de una manera torpe
20 year old kids and so on how are there not going to be
chavales de 20 años y demás cómo no va a
episodes and conflicts and things like that
haber episodios y conflictos y cosas así
but right now there is a part that is
pero ahora mismo hay una parte que la
very very very very very
tiene muy muy muy muy muy
complicated very very very complicated not very very very
complicada muy muy muy complicada no muy
complicated It's not fatal By the
muy muy complicada No lo tiene fatal Por
way, see here above I can't point
cierto veis aquí arriba no puedo señalar
with the let's see with the pliers I can't
con las a ver con las tenazas no puedo
point okay but you see that thumbnail
señalar vale pero veis esa miniatura ahí
up there in large size that is embarrassing
arriba en grande que pone vergüenza
well this  this begoña jpe I met her the
bueno esta esta begoña jpe la conocí el
other day and I was doing a live
otro día y estuve haciendo un directo
with her
con ella
and I was doing a live with her on
e estuve haciendo un directo con ella en
telesalseo check it out because it was
telesalseo miraros porque quedó
spectacular spectacular
espectacular espectacular una
wonderful let's see what things she brings me to my
maravillosa a ver qué cositas me trae mi
places and it's the first 12 minutes they
lugares y es los primeros 12 minutos me
tell me places to
dicen lugares que
see Oh yeah of course because the other is
vea Ah sí claro porque lo otro ya
worth it well Dallas just uploaded a
vale bueno Dallas acaba de subir un
video dismantling and pointing well she
vídeo desmontando y señalando bueno ha
uploaded a video dismantling the
subido un vídeo desmontando el caso
Jenny rubiales and Luis case
Jenny rubiales y Luis
beautiful my goodness
hermoso madre mía
eh well we're not going to see that part I
eh bueno esa parte no la vamos a ver os
recommend that you watch it on her channel okay
recomiendo que la veáis en su canal vale
let's see here the part that she dedicates
vamos a ver aquí la parte que le dedica
to ibai And basically ivai has been
a ibai Y es que básicamente ivai ha sido
a complete fake eh I mean ivai doesn't
un completo falso eh o sea ivai no se
hold back when it comes to being a hypocrite it looks
corta ya un pelo en ser un hipócrita
good and I'm not really saying it eh I
bien queda y no lo digo de verdad eh No
have nothing personal against him and he
tengo nada personal en contra de él y él
knows it But man ivay I had the
lo sabe Pero tío ivay que tuve los
salseo channels and I wouldn't be surprised if
canales de salseo y no me extrañaría que
you saw This video you don't hold back
vieras Este vídeo no te cortas un pelo
eh I mean you don't give a damn and he goes
ya eh o sea te la suda por completo y va
and says Well they see me m 4 million
y dirá Bueno a mí me ven m 4 millones de
people each video Well, what do I
personas cada vídeo Pues a mí que me
care if a million people realize
importa que un millón de personas se den
how hypocritical I am
cuenta de lo hipócrita que soy
if the other 4 million people aren't
si los otros 4 millones de personas no
going to find out And they aren't going to realize
se van a enterar Y no van a darse cuenta
the contradiction and the other million who do
de la contradicción y el otro millón que
know are going to continue consuming me
si lo saben me van a seguir consumiendo
because of the other content I make I mean, what a
por el otro contenido que hago O sea qué
nerve man I mean, what a
cara tan dura tío O sea qué cara tan
nerve you start condemning rubiales
dura ponerte a condenar a rubiales
saying the embarrassment that we
diciendo el bochorno que estamos pasando
Spaniards are going through because of rubiales What an
los españoles por culpa de rubiales Qué
embarrassment we are going through because of
bochorno estamos pasando por culpa de
rubiales that I am going through an embarrassment I don't give a damn what
rubiales que yo estoy pasando un
that guy did, let him
hecho ese tío el bochorno que lo pase Él
and his family be embarrassed I will be embarrassed by what
y su familia Yo Pasaré bochorno por lo
I or someone I care about does or
yo o alguien que me importe o sea
someone I care about either I mean, it
alguien que me importe tampoco o sea
depends no but I get upset and you're all
depende no pero yo vochorno pues y vais
super indignant about the embarrassment that
super indignado el bochorno que nos está
rubiales is putting us through you
haciendo pasar rubiales bochorno te
should be embarrassed by what happens at your
debería de dar lo que pase en tus
events For example at the
eventos Como por ejemplo en la velada
yb evening it is the most hypocritical thing there is
yb es la cosa más hipócrita que hay
many of you already know this  hypocrite dude and he's
muchos ya sabéis esto hipócrita tío y es
very hypocritical he's very false given
muy hipócrita es muy falso dado cuenta
this information so obvious others
de esta información tan evidente otros
still don't And for those who still
todavía no Y para los que todavía
think he's a good person and
pensáis que es una buena persona y
really isn't doing anything wrong I
realmente no está haciendo nada malo de
really challenge you To watch this entire video
verdad os reto A ver este vídeo completo
and after finishing it tell me if
y después de terminarlo me decís si
you really dare to continue saying that
realmente os atrevéis a seguir diciendo
throughout this last one well
eso a lo largo de este último bueno
regarding whether he is a good or bad
respecto a si es una buena o mala
person let's see one You can be false
persona a ver una Tú puedes ser falso
you can be a hypocrite it looks good and so on well I would
puedes ser hipócrita bien queda y demás
n't know If that means
bueno No sabría yo Si eso quiere decir
that you are a good or bad
que seas buena o mala
person I don't think that I don't think being
persona no creo que no creo que ser
false or hypocritical or it looks good
falso o hipócrita o bien
can determine that you are a bad or a
queda pueda determinar que seas mala o
good person or whatever I think I think there are
Buena persona o sea Creo
other things that
que creo que hay otras cosas que
determine that the harm that you want to do
determinan eso el daño que les quieras
to others I think he may have
hacer a los demás creo que ha podido
done things and it goes that are wrong and that they
hacer cosas y va que estén mal y que
could be a bad person but I would
puedan ser de mala persona pero todavía
n't
no me
dare yet for example I wouldn't
atrevería yo por ejemplo todavía no me
dare to sign if he is a bad
atrevería a firmar si es mala
person I consider a bad person for
persona yo considero mala persona por
example I would dare to affirm that nimu
ejemplo me atrevería a afirmar que nimu
is a bad person Hey we will give him
es una mala persona Oye que le daremos
a chance or a second
una oportunidad o una segunda
chance or not it depends on what
oportunidad o no depende de lo que
we hear in  that podcast that's going to come out,
escuchemos en ese podcast que va a salir
by the way, you're going to have the exclusive
que por cierto la exclusiva la Vais a
here, eh, the teaser comes out here on
tener aquí eh el teaser sale aquí en
Javi
Javi
canijo, nimu, for me, is a bad person,
canijo nimu para mí es una mala persona
bad person
malí persona
IV, I IV see him as false, very false, very
IV yo IV lo veo falso muy falso muy
false, very good, it looks good, but something that
falso muy bien queda pero algo que me
makes me determine him, or rather, something that makes me
haga determinarle o sea algo que me haga
define him as a bad
definirlo como mala
person. Family, you would consider that he
persona Familia ustedes consideraría que
is a bad, bad person, for me, for
es una mala mala persona para mí por
example, for me, I am an I, no, sorry
ejemplo para mí I es una I no perdón
for M,
para M
nimu is a bad person, I give it to him, I am an example, no,
nimu es una mala persona yo lo deu yo lo
no, I will tell you the word, how not to
no no lo te diré la palabra como no lo
pigeonhole him into something for being a bad person,
encasillar en algo por mala persona lo
pigeonhole him more
encasillar más
for being a coward and for being false more than for being a
por por cobarde y por falso más que por
bad person, to me, a bad person, it
mala persona a mí una mala persona me
seems to me, wismichu, without a doubt, without a doubt, without a
parece wismichu sin duda sin duda sin
doubt, that is a
duda ese es
bad one from here, from the youth, I don't know about from
malo de aquí de la chavalería no sé de
youtubers, from the
de youtubers de la
gentlemen, there yes, I have, there are at least three, at
señoreros ahí sí tengo yo hay un tres
least three that
por lo menos por lo menos tres que para
for me are bad, bad, bad people,
para mí son malos malos malas personas
yes, bad, but here from the youth, from the
sí malas pero aquí de la chavalería de
youth, for me, bad
la chavalería para mí malas
people,
personas
nimu. Ugh, the T is pathetic, the T is pathetic, there is an
nimu Uf el T penoso el T penoso que hay
issue with him  It's sad I think he's a bad
tema con él t penoso creo que es mala
person for
persona por
example
ejemplo
Win michu as I just told you for me
Win michu como os acabo de decir para mí
if he's a bad person Johan planas for me
si es mala persona Johan planas para mí
if he's a bad person yes
si es mala persona sí
totally totally he has the same
totalmente totalmente tiene el mismo
modus operandi as
modus operandis que alguno que hemos que
some of the ones that I think are
algunos de la de los que pienso que son
bad people well youtuber of the
malas personas de bueno youtuber de la
gentlemen like bad person no I don't know no
señoreros como mala persona no no sé no
gr at the moment I'm not going to see it
gr de momento no lo a ver
bad is that one thing is falsehood and
malo es que una cosa es falsedad y
hypocrisy For example there
hipocresía Por ejemplo yo
is Well a youtuber who recently
hay Bueno un youtuber que hace poco me
told me that I was the dog of Dallas I don't know
dijo que yo era el perro de Dallas no sé
what I would not consider him Both a
qué yo ese no lo consideraría Tan tanto
bad person and a fool you know or
mala persona como tonto sabes o sea
short carche bad person I don't think he
corto carche mala persona no creo que
's a bad person I think it's false and
sea mala persona creo que es falso y
but the thing is we have to know how to
pero es que tenemos que saber
differentiate eh one thing is bad
diferenciar eh una cosa son malas
people another thing is false hypocrites
personas otra cosas falsas hipócritas
opportunists
oportunistas
eh
eh
interested scam year everyone has
interesados timo año todo el mundo se ha
realized how extremely
dado cuenta de lo extremadamente
hypocritical ibai has been and the
hipócrita que ha sido ibai y el
beginning of the end was mainly
principio de su fin fue principalmente
with the kku issue a guy who
con el tema de kku un tipo del cual ya
we have already talked about ad nauseam here on
hemos hablado hasta el artazoo aquí en
this channel and what is really
este canal y que lo que realmente es
important about the case  kcu and it really
importante sobre el caso kcu y realmente
proves a lot that the influencers are that
prueba montón es que los influencer es
with koku Yay has given away his
que con lo de koku Yay ha regalado su
image eh I mean he has given away his image and
imagen eh o sea ha regalado su imagen y
now for example he does this to you of
ahora por ejemplo te hace esto de
condemning rubial dude don't even comment on that
condenar a rubial tío ni opines de ese
subject Shut up I mean haven't you realized
tema Cállate O sea no te has dado cuenta
ivai you haven't realized ivai how you
ivai no te has dado cuenta ivai de cómo
have
te has
condemned yourself and for the rest of your life you are going to have to
condenado y para toda la vida vas a
shut up Jai I am a bad
tener que callarte Jai yo soy mala
person no man you just gave me 10
persona no hombre me acabas de dar 10
bucks How are you going to be a bad person All of you
pavos Cómo vas a ser mala persona Todos
who want to donate 10
los que me queréis donar hoy 10
bucks to me today all of you who want to donate
pavos todos los que me queráis donar hoy
10 bucks to me today you are wonderful people you
10 pavos sois unas estupendas personas
are capable of justifying whitewashing or not
son capaces de justificar blanquear o no
condemning whoever you want as long as you
condenar a quien les apetezca con tal de
keep your job I'll quickly put you in
conservar su trabajo os pongo rápido en
context for who it's not that I
contexto para qui no es que yo
sincerely So IB has to so
sinceramente O sea que IB tenga que o
IB's job depends
sea que el trabajo de IB dependa dependa
on
de
cocu to this day I still can't understand
cocu a mí todavía a día de hoy se me
why kb doesn't expel
escapa el motivo por el kb no expulsa a
cocu eh I attribute it to
cocu eh yo lo achaco a
cowardice  and maybe to interests that we don't
cobardía ía y tal vez a intereses que no
know because that of O sea ivai the
conozcamos porque el de O sea ivai la la
race you imagine no yv goes down to
carrera ustedes imaginaros no yv baja a
coscu of the evening which is what I would have
coscu de la velada que es lo que hubiera
done is that I would not have complicated myself
hecho yo es que no me hubiera complicado
even a hair Come on, I mean, I have an
ni un pelo Vamos o sea yo tengo un
event and at the event there is this guy with
evento y en el evento está este tío con
that with that involved Look I'm sorry
ese con eso implicado Mira Lo siento
friend take it as you want but I
amigo tómatelo como tú quieras pero te
have to get you out of this event I'm not going
tengo que sacar de este evento no te voy
to put you on top of the protagonist of the
a poner encima de protagonista del
Cartel no
Cartel no
What's wrong with ivai who's going to jump on him the
Qué le pasa a ivai se le va a echar
c Army on top of him okay And what do you think is
quién la c Army encima vale Y qué creéis
going to sink ivai for me it's something
que va a hundir a ivai para mí es algo
of cowardice for
de cobardía para
me the lawyer of ass cowarded
mí el abogado de culo acobardó
surely with some clause I am a bad
seguramente con alguna clausula soy mala
person I don't have money man is
persona no tengo dinero hombre es que
that not 10 bucks no I don't know how much that is
eso no son 10 pavos no no sé cuánto es
but surely it is little JP
eso pero seguramente sea poco JP
surely yes that you are a bit of a bad
seguramente sí que seas un poco mala
person
persona
m I want your body I see more of cowardice or
m quiero tu cuerpo veo más a cobardía o
maybe that you have some kind of
a lo mejor que tenga algún tipo de
contacts with soccer players I don't know the
contactos con futbolistas No lo sé la
truth But somewhere he owes something
verdad Pero por algún lado le debe algo
to czu somewhere that I don't know he
a czu por algún lado que desconozco le
owes something to czu to  have that cowardice
debe algo a czu para tener esa cobardía
But I'm not risking my event man they've
Pero es que yo no me juego mi evento tío
lost a sponsor I'm not risking my
han perdido sponsor Yo no me juego mi
event or I mean the real reason really escapes me
evento o sea realmente se me escapa el
eh but it will come out it will
motivo real eh pero saldrá saldrá
always come out everything always comes out with the passage
siempre todo sale siempre con el paso
of time everything comes out I am not informed
del tiempo todo sale No estoy informado
of this and whoever wants to skip to this
de esto y quien se quiera saltar a esta
part can skip to this minute when I
parte puede saltar a este minuto cu
finish talking about it the
termino de hablar de eso el caso de
kosku case is basically one of the
kosku básicamente es uno de los casos
strongest cases In my opinion that has
más fuertes En mi opinión que ha
happened with influencers because there
ocurrido con los influencers porque
are usually many funas
habitualmente hay muchas funas para
up and down of people accusing
arriba y para abajo de gente acusando
many times without proof of any
muchas veces sin pruebas de cualquier
type of abuse but in the case
tipo de abu sos pero es que en el caso
of kcu it is the only one where he alone [ __ ]
de kcu es el único donde él solito se fó
himself he spread the photo of a girl
a sí mismo difundió la foto de una chica
who was unconscious under the effects
que estaba inconsciente bajo los efectos
of drugs ahem ahem gas and after having
de las dro ejem ejem gas y después de
had relations with her while she
haber mantenido relaciones con ella
was already unconscious and not remembering
estando ya inconsciente y no recordando
absolutely anything this photo that was also
absolutamente nada esta foto que además
leaked he made it public And he had a
filtró la hizo públicamente Y tuvo un
where he started to do it to her The came
donde más se ponía a hacerle El came
jameja to her while she was
jameja a ella mientras estaba
unconscious in her bed previously he
inconsciente en su cama anteriormente le
had taken off the clothes that covered her to
había quitado la ropa que la tapaba para
take a photo of her without clothes unconscious
hacerle una foto sin ropa inconsciente
send it to her  her friend make fun of her
mandársela a su amigo burlarse de ella
after insulting her on several streams that is to
después insultarla en varios streams es
say a real abuser through and through
decir un auténtico abusador en toda
without any doubt No you didn't
regla sin ningún tipo de dudas No no te
behave like a daughter of 1 equal in
portaste como una hija de 1 igual en el
sex 10
sexo 10
points
puntosa
and your clothes
e tu ropa
Hey well I wasn't going to say something stupid and
Oye bueno no iba a decir una tontería y
[ __ ] it's that I was going to say that I liked
[__] es que iba a decir que me gustaba
the Simba sweatshirt if you could give it to me
la sudadera de Simba si me la podíais
but I don't know if it would look
regalar pero ya no sé yo si me quedaría
good on me to wear a sweatshirt I tried to
bien ponerme una sudadera yo te intenté
put the bra on you so you wouldn't be
poner el corpiño para que no estés en
naked and and I put it on you But you
pelotas y y te lo puse Pero te lo
took it off by yourself I don't
sacaste solo no
know the girl completely unconscious
sé la chica completamente inconsciente
dude look look making fun of
tío mira mira burlando s de
her I think she was going to and used kcu For
ella yo pienso que iba y uso a kcu Para
good or bad publicity that's why she doesn't
publicidad buena o mala por eso ya no le
talk to him anymore but the thing is that cocu no longer
habla pero es que es que cocu ya no
had that repercussion cocu has
tenía esa repercusión cocu ha vuelto a
had a little bit of good again czu has
tener un poco de bueno czu ha vuelto a
had quite a repercussion again for having been
tener bastante repercusión por haber
at the evening cocu was no longer
estado en la velada cocu ya no estaba
where she was before eh That's my
donde estaba antiguamente eh Esa es mi
first time being with a
primera vez que estoy con una
girl eh
chica eh
[Music]
[Música]
How do you
Cómo se
say it breaks down it breaks down and The
dice se descompone se descompone e La
best part was when  you
mejor parte fue cuando me
told me super earth I don't remember I don't
decías super tierra no me acuerdo No me
remember what I don't remember I don't remember
acuerdo qué no me acuerdo no me acuerdo
well many influencers have been able to be
pues muchos influencers han sido capaces
founded before condemning kcu
de ser funados antes que condenar a kcu
in fact many of them have defended
es más muchos de ellos lo han defendido
cases like for example AR
casos Como por ejemplo el de AR
Gameplays which said but stop
Gameplays la cual dijo pero dejen de
[ __ ] around because of things from the past what else did
cachar por cosas del pasado qué más lo
ccu do but kcu has done some really
hiciera ccu pero kcu ha hecho cosas bien
ugly things and that has to do with him
feas y eso que tiene que ver con que
going to fight at the evening of the year
vaya a pelear en la velada del año
number three let's see Stop [ __ ] around because of
número tres a ver Déjense de ganchar por
things from the past What the [ __ ] other
cosas del pasado What the fuck otros
cases look in Ari's case there are for
casos mira en el caso de Ari hay por
example other cases of people who have
ejemplo otros casos de gente que se han
kept quiet okay I don't know if you will
callado vale Yo no sé si estaré de
agree with me but I make a clear
acuerdo conmigo pero yo hago una Clara
distinction between people who have
diferencia a personas que se han
kept quiet okay And who have not raised their voices
callado vale Y que no han alzado la voz
and have not protested about this for fear of
y no han protestado por esto por miedo a
doors being closed on them and I can
que se le cierre puertas y lo puedo
even understand it for
llegar incluso a comprender yo por
example in
ejemplo en el caso de
Cristinini's case in Cristinini's case Look I'll
cristinini en el caso de cristinini Mira
explain the difference okay let's see if
os explico la diferencia vale a ver si
you agree with me Maybe it
estáis de acuerdo conmigo A lo mejor os
all seems equally bad to you but
parece a todo igual de malo pero yo por
in my case  Cristi
ejemplo en el caso de Cristi
Nini I see fear that doors will be closed to her
Nini yo veo miedo a que se le cierren
and I differentiate it from the case
las puertas y yo lo diferencio al caso
of
de
play why Because in the case of
play por qué Porque en el caso de
cristinini she does not defend coku
cristinini ella no defiende a coku ella
what she does is not condemn him why Well
lo que hace es no condenarlo por qué
because she does not dare Because if she
Pues porque no se atreve Porque si ella
condemns
condena a
czu or she refuses to work in the
czu o se o se niega a trabajar en la
evening because kocu is there or makes some
velada porque esté kocu o hace algún
kind of comments condemning cocu her
tipo de comentarios condenando a cocu su
boss
jefe
yb with his power can close
yb con su poder puede cerrarle
doors on her and this is very serious but for me
puertas y esto es muy grave pero para mí
here I would
aquí yo a
attribute to cristinini apart from
cristinini le achacar aparte de la
hypocrisy and falsehood what I would
hipocresía y de la falsedad yo a ella lo
blame her for would be
que le a chacarí sería
cowardice but I could come to understand, to
cobardía pero podría llegar a entender a
understand her, I mean being as fair and
entenderla o sea siendo lo más justo y
honest as possible, there are some creators
honesto posible yo hay algunos creadores
who have not condemned cocu that I can
que no han condenado a cocu que puedo
come to understand them Because they can go
llegar a entenderlos Porque pueden pasar
from having a lot and living well to having to
de tener mucho y de vivir bien a tener
stop living
que dejar de vivir
this Look at you for example, let's see, in the
esto Mira tú por ejemplo a ver yo en el
case of cristinini that I believe that she does
caso de cristinini que yo creo que ella
not need debai many doors would be closed to her
no necesita debai se le cerrarían muchas
but I understand that she has fear
puertas pero entiendo que tenga el miedo
but for example, for
pero por ejemplo por
example, a
ejemplo un
karchez you have already  seen what
karchez ya habéis visto lo que la ha
happened to her for betraying a uron Play and in
pasado por traicionar a a uron Play y en
that case the people who
ese caso tenía la razón la gente que ha
canceled karches were right but imagine that
cancelado a karches pero imaginaros que
now that she is surviving for being
ahora que está Sobreviviendo por estar
in ibai's teams imagine that
en los equipos de ibai imaginaros que á
ivai closes the doors to carche it is
carche ivai le cierra las puertas ya es
the
la
definitive burial no I
definitiva sepultación no O sea ya es
mean it's see you later mayichi mayichi depends purely and absolutely on ibai mayichi can't fail ibai no way maichi depends on koi and ibai's events without more okay then for example I don't put on the
entonces yo por ejemplo no pongo en el
same side for me for me personally I
mismo para mí para mí personalmente yo a
don't put a maichi and an Ari Gameplays
una maichi y a una Ari Gameplays no la
on the same side why because what
pongo en el mismo lado por qué Porque lo
maichi does is that she keeps quiet out of
que hace maichi es que se calla Por
cowardice and she has reason to be
cobardía y tiene motivos para tener
afraid maichi has plenty of reasons to
miedo maichi tiene de sobra motivos para
be afraid I know that we I know that
para tener miedo sé que nosotros sé que
we say Oh come on condemn her that
nosotros decimos Ay sal condena le que
is false how have you kept quiet about this
es falsa cómo te has callado esto
having a friend What's up but if you
teniendo una amiga Qué tal Pero si tú te
see yourself in her position she has plenty of reason
ves en su postura tiene motivo de sobra
to be
para tener
afraid you can go from earning well I do
miedo puedes pasar de estar ganando bien
n't know how much she will earn with everything  what he
no sé cuánto ganará ella con todo lo que
does but imagine he earns between 5 and
hace pero imagínate que gana entre 5 y
10,000 I don't know if you can beat that eh
10,000 No lo sé si te ganar a eso eh
eh it can go from earning it well to it being the
eh puede pasar de ganarlo bien a que sea
end of the networks and having to work
su fin en las redes y tenga que trabajar
a normal job I don't know if he has
en un trabajo normal No sé si tendrá
some kind of
algún tipo de
study but for
estudio pero por
example this crab undervaluing my
ejemplo este cangrejo infravalorando mis
Dominican pesos I'm sorry man I'm sorry
pesos dominicanos Lo siento tío Lo
today I demand that all
siento yo exijo hoy que todos los
superchance be 10 bucks please
superchance sea de 10 pavos por favor
okay please I'm here with my face
vale por favor estoy aquí con la cara
super swollen and 100 operated making
super hinchada y y 100 operado haciendo
an effort to bring you the gossip
un esfuerzo para traeros el chisme
[ __ ] just kidding eh It's a joke I didn't donate if you do
cabrones es broma eh Es broma no doné si
n't want to listen to me No because then they
no queréis escúchame No porque luego me
take my clip do you think I'm
cogen el clip se cree que lo estoy
serious if you don't donate
diciendo en serio que si doná de [__]
great if not nothing happens I don't put
madre que si no no pasa nada yo no pongo
in the same
en el mismo
batch I don't put in the same batch a
lote yo no pongo en el mismo lote a una
maichi as an Ari Gameplay because
maichi que a una Ari Gameplay porque
maichi keeps quiet out of fear mayichi keeps
maichi se calla por miedo mayichi se
quiet out of fear
calla por miedo
of being left with nothing but ar gamepl it's not
a quedarse sin nada pero ar gamepl no es
that he keeps quiet out of fear
que se calle por miedo
arl comes out to defend  coku and ar gaml
arl sale a defender a coku y ar gaml
comes out to defend
sale a defender a
koku Knowing more than
koku Sabiendo más de lo que sabemos
we know Because ar Gameplay knew about
nosotros Porque ar Gameplay sabía lo de
caprim mint we didn't And when she
caprim mint nosotros no Y ella cuando
comes out to defend koku she
sale ahí a defender a koku
knows more than us Because we
sabe más que nosotros Porque Nosotros
know about the girl in the photo but
sabemos lo de la chica de la foto pero
she knows a chapter more about
es que ella sabe un capítulo más lo de
caprim mint and on top of that Ari Gameplays is a
caprim mint y encima Ari Gameplays es
millionaire and doesn't need deb hahaha I just came in
millonaria y no necesita deb jajajaj
and I see the crab
Acabo de entrar y me veo el cangrejo
face crying loud crab
cara llorando fuerte cangrejo corazón
bright heart a kiss
brillante un beso
andra do you understand the big difference
andra me entendéis la gran diferencia
for me it's not the same lot
para mí no es el mismo lote
I can even understand
yo puedo llegar incluso a entender a
maichi Although it seems very bad and very
maichi Aunque me parezca muy mal y muy
hypocritical and everything you
hipócrita y todo lo que
want but for me it's not the same as
queráis pero para mí no es lo mismo que
hari Gameplays it's not the
hari Gameplays no es lo
same It's not the same as an Ari
mismo No es lo mismo que una Ari
Gameplay is that Ari Gameplay comes out and
Gameplay es que Ari Gameplay sale y lo
defends him comes out and defends him Knowing more
defiende sale y lo defiende Sabiendo más
things than us and Ari doesn't have the
cosas que no nosotros y Ari no tiene la
need that Ari has he doesn't have the
necesidad que tiene Ari no tiene la
need that
necesidad que tiene
maichi has maichi who can charge I'm
maichi maichi que puede cobrar estoy
saying 5 and 10,000 and maybe I've
diciendo 5 Y 10.000 y a lo mejor me he
slipped up Maybe he charges  2s or
colado A lo mejor cobra 2s o
3000 and it can go from that to nothing but the thing is
3000 y puede pasar de eso a la nada pero
that hari Gameplay earns
es que hari Gameplay gana
millions it's like nimu which was
millones es como el de nimu la cual fue
able to say coscu is God ccu is God
capaz de decir coscu es God ccu es God
this for example this one I would put it in
esta por ejemplo esta yo la metería en
a third batch that this one is that she is stupid
un tercer lote que esta es que es tonta
or rather this one that is absolutely stupid and
o sea que esta que es tonta del culo y
evil you understand me This is stupid stupid and
mala me entiendes Esta es tonta tonta y
evil is what it is this one is already there
mala es lo que es esta ya
and others like cristinini saying that
está y otras como cristinini diciendo es
I am not a judge does it seem to you that it is
que yo no soy juez te parece que es un
abuse But the thing is that I do not have to
abuso Pero es que yo no tengo que
determine I am not anyone's judge
determinar yo no soy la jueza de nadie
just as you have to determine does it seem to you that it is
igual que tengas determinar te parece
abuse this has to be determined by
que es abus esto tiene que determinarlo
a judge yichi
un juez yichi
basically But if you notice
básicamente Pero si te das cuenta
cristinini does not
cristinini tampoco lo
defend it either She simply does not want to know
defiende Simplemente no quiere saber
anything about the subject it is different an
nada del tema es diferente un vídeo
entire video in which I explained how I
entero en el que expliqué cóm yo la
helped her in a case of abuse towards a
ayudé en un caso de abuso hacia una
friend of hers But on the other hand with kosku she was
amiga suya Pero en cambio a kosku fue
incapable of saying absolutely anything and
incapaz de decir absolutamente nada y
demonstrated her hypocrisy in
demostró su hipocresía en conversaciones
private conversations which By the way she
privadas la cual Por cierto me ha
blocked me after having sent her
bloqueado después de haberle enviado
this last message whoever wants
este último mensaje quien quiera lo
can stop it Juan
puede parar Juan
cognizin which have
cognizin los cuales han demostrado
clearly demonstrated all their hypocrisy In these
claramente toda su hipocresía En estos
cases they are capable of condemning some
casos son capaces de condenar algunas
things but not others at all and all because
cosas pero otras ni de coña y todo por
why By ibai I have some conversations
qué Por ibai tengo unas conversaciones
which I'm not going to show you yet
las cuales todavía no os voy a mostrar
the video is already recorded but they are
el vídeo ya está grabado pero son
conversations that I saw directly in
conversaciones que vi yo directamente en
person and I even had the opportunity
persona y que tuve la oportunidad hasta
to hold the phone with which
de sostener el teléfono con el que
those conversations were from a
estaban esas conversaciones de una
person who was a friend of kcu and coscu
persona que era coleguita de kcu y coscu
told this person that ibai
le decía a esta persona que ibai le
had told him or rather kcu that I
había dicho a él o sea a kcu que yo no
was not condemning kcu for the things that
estaba funando a kcu por las cosas que
kcu was doing but because I
kcu estaba haciendo sino porque yo
wanted to destroy IB and it's like forgive me
quería destruir IB y es como perdóname
forgive me I have to listen to
perdóname esto lo tengo que escuchar de
some things again but not others at
nuevo algunas cosas pero otras ni de
all and all because why By ibay I have some
coña y todo por qué Por ibay tengo unas
conversations which I'm not
conversaciones las cuales todavía no os
going to show you yet the video is already recorded
voy a mostrar el vídeo ya está grabado
but they are conversations that I saw
pero son conversaciones que vi yo
directly Mr. Krabs money money money money
directamente Don Cangrejo dinero dinero
money for the cburg
dinero dinero dinero para las cburg
I have to save Eh So come on those
tengo que ahorrar Eh Así que venga esos
super chat where I can see them Today
super chat que donde yo pueda verlos Hoy
is Javi gun Javi gun Javi nasi Javi
es el Javi gun Javi gun Javi nasi Javi
nasi go go a kiss brendy  Thank you very much, do
nasi go go un beso brendy Muchas gracias
n't you find it curious how
no se te hace curioso como los
Argentinians [ __ ] on VAT and how coscu
argentinos se kagan en IVA y como coscu
threatening him with lawyers forcing him to
amenazándolo con abogados obligándolo a
enter events stealing the evening
meterlo a eventos robándole la velada
to do it in Argentina Sprint
para hacerla en Argentina Sprint
rejecting IV and making fun of him and
rechazándola a IV y burlándose de él y
the Spanish fear karma will act eh
los españoles miedo el karmma actuará eh
take charge that Karma
haceros cargo de que el Karma
will act personally and that I even had the
actuará mente en persona y que tuve la
opportunity to hold the t
oportunidad hasta de sostener el t
with Javi you are to
con Javi estás para
eat a kiss Melisa beautiful there were
comerte un beso Melisa guapa estaban
those conversations of a person who
esas conversaciones de una persona que
was a friend of coscu let's see a
era coleguita de coscu a ver un
friend of ccu and kcu told this
coleguita de ccu y kcu le decía a esta
person that ibai had told him or
persona que ibai le había dicho a él o
rather kku that I was not denouncing kku
sea a kku que yo no estaba funando a kku
for the things that kku was doing
por las cosas que kku estaba haciendo
but because I wanted to destroy
sino porque yo quería destruir a
i but of course this could be something that I will be
i pero claro esto puede ser algo que
counting on It's that I would
vaya contando con
n't fight with ccu's word
Es que yoo de la palabra de ccu tampoco
either, I mean dasas has seen some
me pelearía o sea dasas ha visto unas
conversations between cocu and a
conversaciones de cocu con un
friend of
coleguita de
cocu in which cocu says that ivai
cocu en el que cocu dice que ivai le
told him let's see it could also be  true
dijo a ver también podría ser verdad
But it could also be a lie from czu
Pero también podría ser mentira de czu
no that ivai said you calm down cocu
no que ivai haya dicho tú tranquilo cocu
that they are not denouncing you for that they
que a ti no te están funando por eso te
are denouncing you for m and it's like what
están funando por m y es como qué
[Music]
[Música]
yv is not only the most hypocritical thing there
yv ya no es solo la cosa más hipócrita
is but also The most
que hay sino también La cosa más
egocentric thing there is yv I know that you are going to see
egocéntrica que hay yv sé que vas a ver
this video as you see them all and
este vídeo como te los ves todos y
let me tell you that your stupid event of
déjame decirte que tu evento estúpido de
the evening I care less than anything but the thing
la velada me importa menos que nada pero
is that apart apart apart let's see
es que aparte aparte aparte vamos a ver
the subject of ccu was already being canceled
el tema de ccu ya se estaba cancelando
before the truth of the evening I mean
de antes de la verdad de la velada O sea
the icing on the cake the icing on the cake knowing that
la guinda la guinda esquiva sabiendo que
this character has that history I
este personaje tiene ese historial
take it and the thing and make him the
lo coja y lo y lo y lo ponga de
protagonist it just doesn't make sense
protagonista es que no tiene sentido
you know it seems even childish to me to
sabes que me parece incluso infantil
start saying Oh no but Dallas does not
ponerte a decir Ay no pero Dallas no
condemn cocu it is it is for the evening Mister
condena cocu es es por la velada Mister
acho Thank you very much welcome
acho Muchísimas gracias bienvenido
how many times did they start saying
cuánto Cuántas veces se pusieron a decir
that when the evening was over
que cuando terminase la velada ya no se
the subject of ccu would not be brought up anymore no no no no
sacaría más el tema de ccu no no no no
no this is for Cancelling and go this is for
no esto es por Cancelar y va esto es por
ruining the evening and
joderle la velada y va en el momento que
It's going to be as soon as the evening is over Nobody's going to talk about this anymore What are you talking about man Are you talking about I never thought I'd see the puny one turned into the crab I confess that I liked the plantain Oliveira a little more but Javi always wants to hear him in any way
apetece escucharlo en cualquier forma
Well I'll think about it I think that here at the
Bueno ya me lo pensaré yo creo que aquí
puny one during this week we're going to
en el canijo durante esta semana vamos a
do the
hacer el
crab and in the in the
cangrejo y en la en la
gentlemen we'll see we'll see about the
señoreros ya veremos ya veremos de los
previous two I didn't say absolutely
dos anteriores No dije absolutamente
anything good about the one about the previous one
nada bueno de la de la anterior
egocentric what's there and I know that you're going to watch
egocéntrica qu hay y sé que vas a ver
this video like all the others and let me
este vídeo como los todos y déjame
tell you that your stupid event of the
decirte que tu evento estúpido de la
evening matters less to me than anything about the
velada me importa menos que nada de los
previous two I didn't say absolutely
dos anteriores No dije absolutamente
anything good at the second event he criticized
nada bueno en el evento segundo criticó
Ari but I don't think it had to do
a Ari pero no creo que tuviera que ver
with the evening yes it's true that I yes it
con la velada sí que es verdad que yo sí
's true that I remember that right
que es verdad que recuerdo que justo
when he canceled it he made the video that
e cuando la canceló que le hizo el vídeo
was if not the day of the evening the
aquel fue si no el día de la velada el
day before I don't know if he did it to
día antes no sé si lo hizo para
screw it up on purpose it was a coincidence
fastidiarla a propósito fue casualidad
m but of the event as such or rather of
m pero del evento como tal o sea de
making a campaign against the event as
hacer una campaña contra el evento como
such no no and  of the first
tal no no y del primero
less and of the first even less I think he
menos y del primero menos incluso Creo
was commenting on both
que creo que estuvo comentando ambos
events on Twitter eh
eventos por por Twitter eh
Ivan Thank you very much Yes yes there are
Iván Muchísimas
people who
gracias Sí sí es que hay gente como que
say that Dallas wants to cancel all the events
dice que el Dallas todos los eventos
Jaime
debai los quiere cancelar Jaime
Welcome to the family but of course
Bienvenido a la familia pero como no el
last year he criticized or rather made a
año pasado criticó o sea le hizo una
joke Ari exposed Ari for the gentlemen
funa Ari expuso a Ari para la señoreros
appropriate to be a talking chili
apropiado ser una guindilla parlante
but the banana is very you too I'll
pero el plátano es muy tú también te
leave you in podcast mode because I'm going to sleep
dejo en modo podcast que me voy a dormir
throwing kisses biceps kiss a kiss eh
lanzando besos bíceps beso un beso eh
well we'll change surely
bueno iremos cambiando seguramente
we'll change characters during the
iremos cambiando de personaje durante la
week for laughs no let's see Ari
semana por las risas no a ver Ari la
exposed her for other topics okay they are
expuso por otros temas vale que son
topics that are topics that
temas
are true okay another
que son temas que son veraces vale otra
thing are the ways to me for example there
cosa son las formas a mí por ejemplo
were ways in that video that I didn't like
hubo formas en ese vídeo que no me
I've always said that okay
gustaron eso lo he dicho yo siempre vale
eh but what Dallas comments on are
eh pero lo que Comenta Dallas son temas
very truthful topics the conversations that he
muy veraces las conversaciones que
shows and the accounts that he shows and so on
enseña y las cuentas que enseña y demás
eh but I don't think that was a
eh pero no creo que eso fueron
cancellation of the evening as they say no it's not
cancelación a la velada como dicen no no
that last year he did it to Ari it's that
es que el año pasado se lo hizo a Ari es
the other one it doesn't matter or  sea ​​Dallas has not
que el otro da igual o sea Dallas no ha
done any campaign against Neither of
hecho ninguna campaña contra Ninguno de
the other two events has been talked about
los otros dos eventos se ha hablado de
this one but it was Obvious meaning there is
este pero es que era Obvio o sea es que
no logical reason for you to have
no hay motivo lógico para que tú tengas
that person as the protagonist in the
a esa persona de protagonista en la
evening And if I said something about this last one it
velada Y si dije algo sobre este último
was because of coscu not because of you you piece of
eraa por coscu no por ti pedazo de
egocentric you'll see Coming soon these
egocéntrico ya veréis Próximamente estas
conversations the video is already recorded
conversaciones el vídeo ya está grabado
and I will show it to you here also on the
y os lo enseñaré aquí tamb también en el
channel but I want you to see this clip of
canal pero quiero que veáis este clip de
how ibai is dedicated to
cóm ibai se dedica a condenar
strongly condemning rubiales and this is where we
enérgicamente a rubiales y aquí es donde
start to talk about the rubiales case and
entramos a hablar del caso rubiales y
watch out because here things get tough tough
ojo que aquí se pone dura dura la
But before I start I must
verdura Pero antes de comenzar debo
tell you that subscriptions are
decirte que las suscripciones están
totally closed you can no longer
totalmente cerradas ya no te puedes
subscribe to the Channel And the thing is that only
suscribir al Canal Y es que solo los
veterans of the Channel the really
veteranos del Canal la gente realmente
intelligent people the ones who saw long before
inteligente la que vio mucho antes que
the rest of the people Who is really the
el resto de gente Quién es realmente el
hypocrite divai can remain
hipócrita divai pueden permanecer aquí
subscribed here all those new to the channel
suscritos todos los nuevos en el canal
who did not arrive in time to be
que no llegaron a tiempo para formar
part of this select Club of the
parte de este selecto Club de la gente
truly intelligent people of
verdaderamente inteligente de redes
social networks will have no choice but to
sociales no les quedará otra que revisar
manually check if I have uploaded videos on  the
manualmente si he subido vídeos en los
review channels Dr inf filters and
canales de la review Dr inf filtros y
What the game everyone else who
What the game todos los demás que no
isn't the veterans Oh how nice the
sois los veteranos Oh qué bonita la
edition eh you'll have to settle for
edición eh tendréis que conformar con
that because in this select Club we only
eso porque en este selecto Club solo
want the best and now yes Let's
queremos a los mejores y ahora sí
start with today's video now we'll
Comencemos con el vídeo de hoy ahora se
talk a little bit about the Rubiales case
hablaré un poquito del caso de rubiales
But first of all a very small
Pero antes que nada un pequeñísimo
summary The Rubiales case is a
resumen El caso rubiales es un
president of a football thing that
presidente de una cosa de fútbol que
basically after the
básicamente después de que el mundial de
women's world cup was won by Spain the
fútbol femenino lo ganase España el
Spanish women's team well this
equipo español femenino pues este
president who is a bald guy
presidente que es un tío calvo le dio un
kissed the number 10 of the team this has
beso a la número 10 del equipo esto ha
caused many politicians in Spain
provocado que muchos políticos en España
and a lot of people who consider themselves
y un montón de gente que se considera
hyper mega Ultra feminist to dedicate themselves to
hiper mega Ultra feminista se dedique a
condemning this kiss that he gave
condenar el beso este que le dio
saying what's wrong with Fran
diciendo que qué le pasa a Fran
Beatriz now I look at it was all non-
Beatriz ahora lo miro fue todo no
consensual what we saw was an
consentido lo que vimos fue un gesto
unacceptable gesture and now we are going to investigate
inaceptable y ahora vamos a investigar
a little more about this because I'm going to
un poquito más sobre esto porque voy a
tell you the truth the question is that that
deciros la verdad la cuestión es que eso
was all it was a
fue todo lo que fue un pico
supposedly non-consensual peak now
supuestamente ente no consentido ahora
we will see that eai has had these words
veremos eso eai ha tenido estas palabras
among many others to condemn this
entre muchas otras para condenar este
act  atrocious of rubiales By the way, the
acto atroz de rubiales Por cierto el
height of being bald is no longer not having a single
colmo de un calvo ya no es no tener un
stupid hair, it's having the last name
pelo de tonto es apellidarse
rubiales, what nonsense this
rubiales qué tontería esta
bastard, what nonsense I really want you to
cabrón qué tontería de verdad quiero que
listen to this mass of
escuchéis a esta masa de hipocresía
cheap hypocrisy that is speaking next
barata que está hablando a continuación
today it came out By the way, they have
hoy ha salido Por cierto que han eh
disqualified Luis Rubiales from
inhabilitado a Luis rubiales desde la
FIFA after Well, the embarrassment and
FIFA después de Bueno pues el bochorno y
the terrible ridicule that he is
el ridículo espantoso que nos está
making us all go through, the embarrassment, the
haciendo pasar a todos el bochorno el
embarrassment and the terrible ridicule that he
bochorno y el ridículo espantoso que nos
is making us all go through, man I
está haciendo pasar a todos tío Es que a
would like I would love
gustaría a mí me encantaría
eh What embarrassment he is making me go through
eh Qué bochorno me está haciendo pasar a
rubiales what what embarrassment he is not
rubiales qué qué bochor no me está
making me go through
haciendo pasar a m
rubiales what the [ __ ] do I care what
rubiales m qué [__] me importa lo que
that guy is
ese tío est
doing and
haciendo y
then
luego
one thing that surprised me Is that de
una cosa que me ha sorprendió Es que de
la Fuente also said Hey, I
la Fuente también ha dicho Oye yo
condemn this attitude without palliatives, well I
condeno esta actitud sin paliativos pues
say but if de la Fuente was He was one
digo pero si de la Fuente estaba Era uno
of those who was applauding yesterday and he goes
de los que estaba aplaudiendo ayer y va
and goes pointing out the hypocrisy of the
y va ir señalando la hipocresía de los
others eh touch your nose we have not
demás eh tócate las naric no nos hemos
become  all completely crazy
vuelto todos completamente locos de la
I don't understand anything good they have
cabeza yo no entiendo nada bueno lo han
disqualified him for 90 days but it is true that
inhabilitado 90 días pero es verdad que
now the superior sports committee comes in
ahora entra el comité superior de
if I'm not mistaken it is not called
deportes si no me equivoco no se llama
CSD And from there supposedly this
csd Y a partir de ahí supuestamente esto
Well then they are going to follow a
Bueno pues van van a seguir una una
series of parameters a series of steps to
serie de parámetros una serie de pasos a
follow so that they said eh I read Victor
seguir para que decían eh leía a Víctor
Navarro that on Wednesday eh
Navarro que el miércoles eh estuviese eh
Rubiales was out I mean not only do you say that
rubiales fuera O sea no solo dices que
what he did is disgusting and you condemn him
es asqueroso lo que hizo y lo condenas
energetically and you open Stream just
de forma enérgica y abres Stream solo
to say this atrocity but
para decir esta barbaridad sino que
on top of that you want the bald guy Rubiales to
encima quieres que el calvo rubiales
lose his job forever and b the one who
pierda el trabajo para siempre yb el que
gave him a salary and made
le puso un sueldo y convirtió en evento
Coscu the main event a guy who spread
principal a coscu un tipo que difundió
the photo of an unconscious girl who had
la foto de una chica inconsciente la
had relations with her and
cual había tenido relaciones con ella y
she didn't even remember while she was looking for
ella ni se acordaba mientras itaba por
help while they were supposedly
ayuda mientras supuestamente estaban
having relations all this in an
manteniendo relaciones todo esto en un
absolutely public case that ibai
caso absolutamente público eso ibai lo
turns it into the Mine event Ah but it
convierte en el Mine event Ah pero
ends there no no no it doesn't end there
termina ahí no no no termina ahí
while ibai was doing m event for
mientras ibai estaba haciendo m event a
his little friend at the evening who has
su amiguito en la velada el cual tiene
a lot of  pictures with him and they met
un montón de fotitos con él y conocieron
Messi together and they had a threesome
a Messi juntos y se montaron un trío
Go figure what's going on I remind you that
Vete a sa ver qué cosas os recuerdo que
Ivai was also there for the last few
ivai además estuvo Durante los últimos
years also laughing at the fact that I was going to
años también riéndose de que yo fuese a
lose my job forever mocking
perder mi trabajo para siempre mofándose
that I had lost my
que yo hubiese perdido el canal en
Twitch channel and making fun of me going to
Twitch y burlándose de que yo fuese a la
jail I hadn't thought of this
cárcel no había caído en esto esto no lo
I hadn't mentioned this the other day eh But
había comentado yo el otro día eh Pero
this is [ __ ] true
esto es verdad [__]
Ivai during the funa to Dallas he was
ivai por la funa a Dallas se estuvo
making fun of it yes it's true that it was 5
mofando que sí que es verdad que hace 5
years ago but I think IV doesn't
años pero yo creo que IV no se
regret it I mean he hasn't had a single
arrepiente O sea no ha tenido ni una
bit of regret because he doesn't
pisa de arrepentimiento porque no se
regret it and he goes during the funa to Dallas they
arrepiente y va durante la funa a Dallas
were celebrating and he was happy that
se festejaba y se alegraba de que a
Dallas was left without a channel and without a
Dallas lo dejaran sin canal y sin
job and in jail and all that [ __ ]
trabajo y en la cárcel y todas esas
[ __ ] I hadn't thought of this you
cosas [__] no había caído en esto tú
but do you think that the
pero creéis que el
Mr. Crab case Tell the
caso señor cangrejo Dígale al viejo
tasty old man that we love him I will tell him from
sabroso que lo queremos se lo diré de
you but he has asked me
vuestra parte pero me ha pedido por
please that all of you who are watching
favor que todos los que estéis viendo
this live to do  members that
este directo que os hagáis miembros que
we have dropped below 3000 members it would make
hemos bajado de los 3000 miembros
Javi very excited when he
le haría mucha ilusión a Javi cuando
comes back next week to find
vuelva la semana que viene encontrarse
3000 members okay And not members of what
con 3000 miembros vale Y no miembros de
you think please mine and
los que ustedes pensáis por favor mío y
coscu that's the only thing
de coscu es lo único que es la
ibai's hypocrisy is no no if it doesn't
hipocresía de ibai no no si es que aquí
end here I take this opportunity to remind you
no termina aprovecho para recordaros
when ibai expelled two people from his super
cuando ibai expulsó de su grupo super
cool group of coi streamers
guay de streamers de coi a dos personas
just for giving likes to girls who
únicamente por dar likes a chicas que
had only ones literally This was
tenían only literalmente Esto fue
a boy and a girl entered his
entraron un chico y una chica en su
group and it was discovered that the girl was
grupo y se descubrió que la chica le
saying comments flirting with another
decía comentarios ligando a otro
streamer and the boy was giving likes to
streamer y el chico le daba like a
girls who had only ones and this was enough for
chicas que tenían only y esto bastó para
him to even condemn them publicly and
él hasta condenarlos públicamente y
put a TT saying I don't know how I
poner un TT diciendo no sé cómo se me ha
missed it You've already done it effectively I
pasado Ya lo has hecho efectivamente
think we did things extremely
creo que hicimos las cosas rematadamente
wrong but there are many more cases if
mal pero hay muchos casos más si
we want to talk specifically about
queremos hablar específicamente de besos
non-consensual kisses we can look at this case for
no consentidos podemos ver este caso por
example maybe you will remember it's not that
ejemplo a lo mejor os acordaréis no es
I have a girlfriend that's okay Oh nothing's wrong
que tengo novioa que no pasa nada Ah no
Give me a peck no that I have a
pasa nada Dame un pico no que tengo
boyfriend and the other saying nothing's wrong your
novio y el otro diciendo no pasa nada tu
boyfriend  no my boyfriend is that I am respectful
novio no mi novio es que yo soy respet
va da da Give me no yes no Paula paulis come
va da da Dame no si no Paula paulis ven
Give Brunete a kiss a crazy kiss for
Dale un beso a brunete un beso loco para
Brunete cla on the cheek Brunete says
brunete cla en la mejilla brunete dice
on the cheek and look what he does he's a
en la mejilla y fijaos lo que hace es
guy Ah Give me more the
tipejo Ah Dame má la
cheek incredible eh what does
mejilla increíble eh qué tendrá que
ibai have to say about this friend of his who
decir ibai ante este coleguita suyo que
gave him an unauthorized kiss he will call it
hizo un beso no consentido lo llamará
shameful he will ask for
bochorno pedirá que le quiten para
this abusive
siempre el trabajo a este abusador
friend of coscu to lose his job forever By the way let's see
amiguito de coscu Por cierto vamos a ver
what you have to say and about this guy
lo que tu que decir y sobre este tipo
called Brunenger friends
que se llama brunenger amigos y amigas
give Brunenger a round of applause
den un aplauso a brunenger
applause Wait, on top of that he invited him to
aplausos Espérate que encima lo invitó a
the year
la velada del año
3 evening the meeting of false feminists and
3 la reunión de los falsos feministas y
abusers bravo bravo ivai bravo when they
abusadores bravo bravo ivai bravo cuando
applaud ibai to get into a place
aplaudan a ibai para entrar en un sitio
they will have to applaud him and
tendrán que aplaudirle a él y a la
his hypocrisy that comes
hipocresía suya que viene
after wow
detrás wow
wow wow I didn't know Oh about
wow wow no sabía Oh lo del beso de
Brunenger's kiss Yes I knew but
brunenger Sí lo sabía pero
no I didn't know that  He went and got along with that one
no no sabía que iba y se llevaba con ese
too wow wow well And Brunenger has
también wow wow bueno Y brunenger tiene
more unfortunate clips eh I mean
más clip desafortunados eh o sea a a
Luna Clark who is a very pretty girl from
Luna Clark que es una chica guapísima de
Twitch eh he also made her uncomfortable like
Twitch eh la la incomodó también como
putting his hands on top of her
poniéndole las manos en lo alto de las
legs I don't know what and Luna had to
piernas no sé qué y Luna le tuvo que
say Hey those confidences please
decir Oye esas confianzas por favor me
take my little hands away from here yes yes yes yes we
quitan las manitas de aquí sí sí sí sí
saw it here he has become a
lo vimos aquí se ha convertido un ente
separate entity a guy who by the way is
aparte un tipo que por cierto se dedica
also dedicated to insulting girls
además también a insultar a las chicas
who refuse to give him a kiss I mean
que se niegan a darle un beso O sea que
by the way with eche with Brunenger
por cierto con eche con el brunenger
this one also cheated on him Lia
este también le puso los cuernos la Lia
sicora the other guy was not said for
sicora al al otro chico no se decía pra
a kiss or you insult them for not giving her a
un beso o las insultas por no darle un
kiss
beso
[Music]
[Música]
he says that's life king and he starts
le dice así es la vida rey y se pone a
insulting him as you were saying And as you were saying
insultarle cómo decías Y cómo decías
friends, give
amigos y amigas den un aplauso a
Brunenger a round of applause go but about
brunenger aplausos vaya pero sobre
rubiales what were you saying rubiales
rubiales que decías rubiales
out to continue the mob to continue
fuera para seguir la turba para seguir
the mob of the government of this
la turba del gobierno de este gobierno
sick government that we have and of this society
enfermo que tenemos y de esta sociedad
that we have that no  it has a solution now and we're
que tenemos que no tiene remedio ya y
going to hell how wonderful
nos vamos a la [__] [__] qué maravilla
ivay the worst of all is that we're going to see
ivay lo peor de todo es que vamos a ver
next how the case of rubiales
a continuación como el caso de rubiales
is very different from that of brunenger and that of
es muy diferente al de brunenger y al de
kku with an impressive difference in
kku con diferencia impresionante de
fact You are going to see next how
hecho Vais a ver a continuación como
rubiales is innocent and you will all be able to see it
rubiales es inocente y podréis verlo
below if he has told you the
todos a continuación si os ha dicho lo
opposite to someone or you have loved each other
contrario a alguien o os habéis quido
before otherwise I am going to show you
antes lo contrario voy a mostraros
proof of how the other chick lies more than she
pruebas de cóm la otra tipa miente más
talks You're going to freak out how it is possible
que habla Vais a flipar cómo es posible
that IV is still in such a
que IV siga estando en una posición tan
good position being so extremely
buena siendo tan extremadamente
hypocritical well that you know why
hipócrita bueno que sepáis porque la
people suck his ass for what he moves and
gente le come el culo por lo que mueve y
what and what it implies and it goes or rather it's
lo que y lo que implica y va o sea es
exactly the same example that I don't
exactamente el mismo ejemplo que que no
know what to put but people there are
sabé queé poneros pero la gente hay
many people who cannot see i eh And they
mucha gente que no puede ver a i eh Y me
come to me and they tell me things about IB
vienen a mí y Me comentan cosas de IB
there are many streamers who cannot and cannot
hay muchos streamers que no pueden y no
stand ibai eh And they come to me and they
soportan al ibai eh Y me vienen y me
tell me a lot of things and they tell me
cuentan un montón de cosas y Me comentan
a lot of things and then I see them there
un montón de cosas y luego los veo allí
with him and I
con él y les
tell them what are you coming  to tell me things about
digo qué vienes a mí a contarme cosas de
and then you're there losing your ass
y luego estás allí perdiendo el culo
playing soccer with him or having a drink
jugando al fútbol con él o tomando algo
with him or you go to his house to the parties he
con él o te vas a su casa a las fiestas
organizes
que organiza
how disgusting really man how disgusting that on
qué asco de verdad tío qué asco que en
several occasions they have tried to denounce the
varias ocasiones han intentado funar lo
various different ones one of them for
varios diferentes uno de ellos por
example was the case of this guy who
ejemplo fue el caso de este chico que
was the one who entered ibai's team and
fue el que entró en el equipo de ibai y
then ibai denounced him and kicked him out of the team
luego ibai lo funo y lo echó del equipo
Oh I ran into this guy in
Ay A este chico Me lo encontré en
person I ran into him at the lake in
persona Me lo encontré en el lago en
Seville I ran into him I greeted him uh I
Sevilla me lo encontré lo saludé eh lo
greeted him I ran into him I don't remember if it
saludé me crucé con él no me acuerdo si
was in the hallway Where did I give Oh I
fue en el pasillo En dónde di Ah te
know you he was about to speak out
conozco estuvo a punto de hablar en
against divai and after I had
contra divai y después de yo haberle
spoken to him how
hablado lo
nice man I saw your video yesterday and well it
bien tío vi ayer tu vídeo y bueno me
moved me a little and I decided to answer
removió un poco y me ha salido contestar
today on Twitter but man water under the bridge in the
hoy por Twitter pero tío agua pasada al
end what really matters to me more
final lo que de verdad me importa más
than anything is being [ __ ] Peace with myself he
que todo es estar [__] Paz conmigo mismo
knows very well how the internet works and
sabe de sobra cómo funciona internet y
right now I'm enjoying the
ahora mismo Estoy disfrutando de las
personal things in my life By the way
cosas personales de mi vida Por cierto
I appreciate you asking about me
agradezco que me hayas preguntado por mí
if you need anything Tell me Well I think it
si necesitas algo Cuéntame Pues yo creo
's a good time  so you can
que es un buen momento para que me
tell me what happened Even if you don't
cuentes lo que pasó Aunque luego no
decide to do anything later I'm more
decidas hacer nada así estoy más
informed of what happened what he did you
informado de lo que sucedió lo que hizo
know was block me he literally
sabéis que fue bloquearme literalmente
blocked me and you also have this case
me bloqueó y también tenéis este caso
of And why does
de Y por qué lo
another different artist block him which
bloquea otro artista diferente el cual
ibai took advantage of him he made a
ibai se aprovechó de él él le hizo un
thread against ibai and when he started to
hilo en contra de ibai y cuando empezó a
gain repercussion ibai went to do
ganar repercusión ibai fue a hacer
damage control and basically make sure he would
control de daños y básicamente hacer que
n't speak badly of him all through his
no hablase mal de él todo a través de su
girlfriend Carmencita who does
novia Carmencita la cual le hace
public relations for him it's an outrage
relaciones públicas es una barbaridad
that and Well basically he got the
eso y Pues básicamente consiguió que el
kid to delete the thread and not
chaval pues borras el hilo y no volviese
speak badly of ibai anymore and here you can see
a hablar más mal de ibai y aquí pues ver
the full conversation if you want to
la conversación completa si queréis pa
use it to read it but in essence the
usarla para leerla pero en esencia el
guy basically ended up
tipo básicamente terminó borrando por
completely deleting Lilo what he did against ibai
completo Lilo que hizo en contra de ibai
why because in the end he manages to do it
por qué porque al final consigue hacerlo
as always he manages to get along with the
de siempre consigue llevarse bien con la
people that suits him and he makes them delete
gente que le conviene y hace que borren
all the things that are against him
todas las cosas que hay en su contra
But you know what ibai is not going to
Pero sabéis qué ibai a mí no me va a
buy me Not today or tomorrow or ever before I'd
comprar Ni hoy ni mañana ni nunca antes
rather be dying of hunger
prefiero estarme muriendo de hambre
under  a bridge to accept a single
debajo de un puente que aceptar un solo
Euro from ibai a guy who has an
Euro de ibai un tipo que tiene un
abuser at his previous event of
abusador de por en su evento anterior de
the evening 3 and who now dedicates himself to
la velada 3 y que ahora se dedica a
condemning rubiales and we are going to analyze
condenar a rubiales y vamos a analizar
the case of rubiales in more depth do
el caso de rubiales más en profundidad
you remember when I
os acordáis cuando os
told you do you remember when I told you when
dije os acordáis cuando os dije cuando
everything from the evening that the topic of
todo lo de la velada que el tema de
rubial Oh the topic of rubial that the topic
rubial Uy el tema de rubial que el tema
of ivai
de ivai
[Music]
[Música]
with the topic of I with what with the
con el tema de I con lo de con lo de la
evening will end up exploding later
velada terminará explotando más adelante
not because of the no because of the topic itself but
no por el no por el tema en sí sino
because there will be moments like this in
porque habrá momentos como este en los
which ivis will want to put a medal on himself
que ivis se querrá poner una medalla y
and he can't he can't do it he can't do it or I mean who the [ __ ] are you and now to go out and talk about rubiales man what balls what balls well and the host does not marry him in the last hours what has come out in the last
horas lo que ha salido en las últimas
hours of cocu affirming that he is no longer a
horas de cocu afirmando que ya no es
friend of
amigo de
IB I mean suddenly they have stopped being
IB o sea de repente han dejado de ser
friends after all this
amigo después de todo esta
movement the only ones that are talking bad
movida los únicos que están hablando mal
about me are people that don't know me
de mí es gente que no me conoce
Latin America was
latinoamérica estaba
moving  around me still with a
moviéndose alrededor mío aú con un
Twitter infested with accusing me of things
Twitter infestado de acusándome de cosas
but that's happened to me my whole life what
pero eso me pasó durante toda mi vida lo
happens is that never at such a
que pasa es que nunca a un nivel tan
serious level as accusing of such an atrocity
grave como acusar de semejante atrocidad
one thing is to be I don't know that your content
una cosa es ser no sé que tu contenido
is for children And to be an idiot and another
sea para nenes Y ser un [__] y otra
thing is that I lived with that my whole life
cosa que es con eso conviví toda mi vida
and I suck a holo you know but the thing is that
y me chupo un holo viste pero es que lo
dibai is going to give him the face dibai is going to
dibai le va a dar la cara lo dibai le va
give him the face Look all his life this is going
a dar la cara Mira toda la vida ya le va
to haunt him I mean having
a perseguir esto O sea haber tenido a
kcu on the poster for the evening is going to
kcu en el cartel de la velada le va a
haunt him all his life All his life and
perseguir toda la vida Toda la vida y
this guy Here giving it or so This is
este chico Aquí dando o sea Es que esto
really what I'm going to be
de verdad es lo que a mí me vamos me
impressed by not that this guy far from
impresiona no que este chico lejos de
apologizing or recognizing the error and
disculparse o de reconocer el error y
having settled the controversy as quickly as possible
haber zanjado la polémica más rápido se
wants to like walk around In
quiera como pasear Por
interviews beating himself in the chest
entrevistas dándose Golpes en el pecho
with his morals or something like that not
con su moral o algo por el estilo no
like the others were wrong And
como que los demás estaban equivocados Y
in some way because he won the
de alguna manera porque ha ganado el
fight the truth has been proven like
combate se ha demostrado la verdad como
people love him because
que la gente lo quiere porque se ha
the truth has been discovered no man and  you did what you
descubierto la verdad no tío y hiciste
did and that's it dude keep a
lo que hiciste y punto tío Vuela un
low profile stay on your channel playing
perfil bajo quédate en tu canal jugando
LoL I know whatever but what the [ __ ] are
al LoL yo que sé lo que sea pero de qué
you doing what the [ __ ] dude not in an
[__] vas de qué [__] tío en una
interview but the others
entrevista no pero es que los demás me
canceled me but they're just people who no
cancelaron pero solo son gente que no
one has to know you those who
que nadie te tiene que conocer que los
know you say worse things Capri
que te conocen hablan cosas peores Capri
mint Capri min met you at an event and
mint Capri min te conoció en un evento y
look at the experience the
mira la experiencia que tiene la
girl has What are you saying
chica Qué dices
man when do you have to explain to your
tío ya cuando le tenés que explicar a tu
old lady Che look on the internet it says that
vieja Che mira en internet se dice que
I'm a that's another Level I didn't
soy un ya eso es otro Level Yo tampoco
jump to defend myself either and I had everything to
salté a defenderme y tenía todo para
defend myself Who is going to have more than me
defenderme Quién va a tener más que yo
to defend myself from something like that but it was
para defenderme de algo así pero era era
the problem I was the first Stream I always
el pedo Yo los primeros Stream siempre
underestimated that I had everything to defend myself
estimé que yo tenía todo para defenderme
but it was the problem Thank you very much brendy
pero era el pedo Muchas gracias brendy
imagine that you have everything to
sea imagínate que tienes todo para
defend yourself and you don't do it
defenderte y no lo
I said that they do what they have to do I
haces dije que hagan lo que tengan que
will take it and when I
hacer yo me la voy a bancar y cuando
have a real problem because that
tenga un problema de verdad porque eso
shouldn't even be a problem I
ni siquiera Debería ser un problema
would be there to respond to it in the
estaría ahí para responderlo de la forma
appropriate way when when it's worth it or rather
que corresponde cuando cuando vale o sea
here what is  meaning he has
aquí lo que está queriendo decir es que
n't sued Dallas nor is he going to, I
no ha demandado a Dallas ni lo va a
already told you but if I did
hacer ya os lo dije pero si es que os lo
tell you if anyone who knows how
dije si es que cualquiera que sabe cómo
trials and
funciona un poquito los juicios y las
lawsuits work knows that cun would
demandas sabe que cun no demandaría a
never sue Dallas because the
Dallas nunca ningún abogado porque el
lawyer would tell him Look if you
abogado se lo exp le diría Mira si tú
sue Probably what you're going to
demandas Probablemente lo que vas a
get is a
conseguir es que haya una
sentence that puts a name to what
sentencia que le ponga nombre a lo que
you did And right now at least Keep
tú hiciste Y ahora mismo por lo menos
this in mind, not the people just to contradict Dallas
Quédate con esto no la gente por
because
llevarle la contraria a Dallas pues
many people just to
mucha gente solamente por llevarle la
contradict
contraria a
Dallas are not going to pay attention
Dallas pues no no van a hacer
to that okay but here coku what he
caso de eso vale pero aquí coku lo que
's saying is that he would defend himself in
está diciendo es que él se defendería en
the event that they sue him that
el caso de que lo demanden a él de que
the girl denounces him and the girl is not
la chica lo denuncias a él y la chica no
going to leave
va a salir
IV he just put up with it to get the
IV no más lo aguantó para sacar el
event out and he already discarded it but ibai didn't
evento y ya lo desechó pero ibai no
need cocu to get the event out
necesitaba de cocu para sacar el evento
iai would have looked better by removing it he
iai hubiera quedado mejor sacándolo
would have been applauded a thousand times more I
hubiera sido mil veces más aplaudido O
mean if b had removed him from the event y b
sea sib lo llega a sacar del evento yb
would be in the perfect position to
estaría en la potestad perfecta para
take it and now  condemn rubiales or
[__] y ahora condenar a rubiales o
say whatever you think about the subject of
decir lo que le parezca el tema de
rubiales because in the end well
rubiales porque al final bueno
you can simply if you think that
simplemente puedes si tú crees que de
rubiales is for them to put him in
rubiales es para que lo metan en la
jail and for the guy to lose his
cárcel y para que el tío pierda el
job It's that you are short you are shorter
trabajo Es que eres corto eres más corto
than the vest that the sleeves of
que el chaleco de la que las mangas del
Jordi Wi's vest But well You can
chaleco de Jordi Wi Pero bueno Tú puedes
be that short no but at least
ser así de corto no pero por lo menos no
you are not a hypocrite and you are not false but ivai did
eres hipócrita y no eres falso pero ivai
not need it ibay did it either out of
no lo necesitaba ibay lo hizo o bien por
cowardice because he was afraid of whatever
cobarde porque le dio miedo lo que lo
these people told him
que fuera que le dijeran esta
or out of some kind of fear or to contradict
gente o por algún tipo de miedo o por
Dallas
llevarle la contraria a Dallas
someone wants to do harm s it was with
alguien quiere hacer daño s era con mala
malice he gives it and gives it and gives it and gives it and it is dismissed and it is
leche le da y le da y le da y le da y se
dismissed and it is
desestima y le da y se desestima y le da
illegal there was nothing there was never anything
ilegal no había nada nunca hubo nada
because of course on social networks everyone
porque claro por redes sociales todos
is But I was always waiting that
son Pero yo siempre estuve esperando que
if someone had something to tell me that I would
si alguien Tenía algo para decirme que
do it the right way and there never
lo haga de la forma correcta y nunca
was but there was not even close to having
hubo pero ni no hubo ni cerca de tener
a problem of that style we were
un problema de ese estilo estábamos
prepared for it to happen because
preparados para que lo haa porque
we would come eventually that that is to say to be
nosotros venía eventualmente que que o
able to Show everything that  we had
sea poder Mostrar todo lo que teníamos
but jumping to clarify something where there wasn't let's say
pero saltar a aclarar algo donde no
you didn't do it, I
había digamos d vos no lo hiciste o
mean I didn't want to jump to clarify something
sea que no quería saltar a aclarar algo
that didn't happen, he says, man, how can that be,
que no pasó dice tío Cómo se puede madre
my goodness, this is it. Thank you IB, eh. And I kind of had to
mía esto Esto es Gracias IB eh Y se tuve
put my chest to the bullets
medio que poner el pecho a los balazos
that rained down because of me, so to speak,
que llovían por culpa mía entre comillas
although I didn't do anything, putting up with all of that, it
aunque yo no hice nada bancarse todo eso
wore down our relationship a lot,
desgastó mucho nuestra relación sin
unintentionally, and we're not friends. Unfortunately,
querer y no somos amigos Lamentablemente
with you and no, you don't talk to each other anymore, you don't have a
con y no no te hablas más no tenés más
relationship anymore, yes, I don't try, but
relación s no intento pero
regardless, everyone I
independientemente que todo el mundo al
ask tells me that he doesn't
que le pregunto me dicen que tampoco les
answer them either, he congratulates me after the
contesta él me felicita después de la
evening, he also tells me you did a Combat,
velada también me dice hiciste un Combat
thanks for
gracias por haber
participating, I mean, let's say it all ended
participado o sea digamos terminó todo
well. And there's like a friendship, but well,
bien Y hay como una amistad pero bueno
people keep asking all the
la gente sigue preguntando todo el
time. Hey, when are you going to do something
tiempo Che Cuándo van a hacer algo
together, how are you with me and so on? I think
juntos cóm andas con i y demás yo creo
everything's going really well, nobody has
que está todo recontra bien nadie tiene
anything against the other person, but it
nada en contra de la otra persona pero
's very difficult to reach him,
es muy difícil llegar a él
nothing, nothing, ivai has done the evening, he
nada nada ivai ha hecho lo de la velada
has maintained it out of stubbornness, look at how div it
ha mantenido por cabezonería mira lo div
could be due to many things, okay,
se puede deber a muchas cosas vale lo de
maintaining czu could be  that he
mantener a czu puede que lo haya
kept him Because he didn't want to agree with
mantenido Por no querer darle la razón a
Dallas, maybe he
Dallas puede que lo haya
kept him for a thousand reasons, okay, it
mantenido por cosas por mil cosas vale
could be because he didn't agree with
podría ser por no darle la razón a
Dallas, it could be, I do
Dallas podría
n't know, honestly, because he didn't agree with him, because he did
ser es que no lo sé la verdad por no
n't back down,
darle la razón por no bajarse del burro
no, and the moment the
no y en el momento que ha terminado la
evening was over, he said, Ugh, I'm getting out of
velada ha dicho Uf este me lo quito de
here with this guy and I'm disassociating myself from him. I
aquí y me voy desvinculando de él es que
sincerely don't understand. I mean,
sinceramente no no entiendo O sea de
really, I don't understand IB's position. I don't
verdad la postura de IB es que no la
understand it, I
entiendo
really do
es que no la entiendo de verdad la
n't understand IB's position. I
postura de IB no la
want to understand it, but it's
entiendo quiero entenderlo pero es
impossible. It seems to me that it's
imposible me da a mí que es
impossible. I didn't do anything, says
imposible Yo no hice nada dice el
Uncle
tío
Ivay, he didn't bring it up to
ivay no lo sacó para llevarle la
contradict
contraria a
Dallas. Look, I've also thought that
Dallas Mira yo he pensado también que
what Adrian Bara says could exist,
podía existir lo que dice Adrián bara
in case they had a contract for the evening, let's
por si tenían un contrato de la velada a
see, maybe there is a contract in which
ver puede que exista un contrato en el
neither party can
que ninguna de las partes puedan
refuse to participate in the event, okay, nor
rechazar participar en el evento vale ni
leave the other party in the lurch, but of course,
dejar tirado a la otra parte pero claro
normally these types of clauses
normalmente ese tipo de cláusulas
involve another clause that tells you that
conllevan otra cláusula que te dice que
there are certain reasons
Hay ciertos motivos en lo
why, in this case, the event.
que en este caso el evento
Yes, I
Sí
could. Yes, I could cancel  the
podría Sí podría cancelar la
participation of cocu is worth for example
participación de cocu vale por ejemplo
in television there is usually a clause that
en la tele suele haber una cláusula que
tells you that if suddenly imagine that
te dice que si de repente Imagínate que
a person suddenly appears who is an
una persona de repente aparece que es un
abuser okay something that tarnishes the
maltratador vale algo que manche la
image of the channel something that tarnishes the
imagen de la cadena algo que manche la
image of the program there is a clause
imagen del programa ahí hay una cláusula
that indicates that you can freely
que te indica que tú puedes libremente
dispense with that person of that
prescindir de esa persona de ese
worker
trabajador
so it would surprise me if that was not
entonces a mí me extrañaría que eso no
leaked Or imagine that or
estuviera filtrado O sea imagínate que o
okay you have a clause that
sea vale tienes una cláusula que te
tells you that there is a penalty in
indica que que hay una penalización en
the case that czu is fired in
el caso de que de que echen a czu en
this case no Well imagine let's give
este caso no Bueno imag vamos a poner
another example imagine there is a
otro ejemplo Imagínate que hay una
clause that
cláusula que
says Hey look you can't you can't
dice Oye pues mira no
fire Manolo because there is
puedes no puedes echar a Manolo porque
a signed clause that pays a
hay una cláusula firmada que paga una
penalty of 100000 And yeah yes he kicks him out if he
penalización de 100000 Y vai si si lo
breaks the contract but of course and
echa si rompe el contrato pero claro y
if suddenly it comes out that Manolo has
si de repente sale que Manolo se ha
broken into a school with a katana and has
metido en un colegio con una catana y ha
started murdering 25
empezado a asesinar a 25
children you can't kick him out of the
niños no lo puedes echar de la
evening there are no clauses for that okay those
velada no hay cláusulas para eso vale
contracts are also usually
los contratos esos además suelen estar
very well tied up and very  well done for
muy bien atados y muy bien hecho para
any type of situation that could
cualquier tipo de situación que pueda
harm the image of the
perjudicar a la la imagen de la de la
organization that is doing the
organización que esté haciendo el
event
evento
okay So that wouldn't fit me
vale Así que no me cuadraría
I think it's fear of
eso yo creo que es miedo a las
retaliation that I may have from
represalias que pueda tener por gente
people from Argentina or fear of
por la gente de Argentina o por miedo a
contacts or whatever
contactos o lo que sea
or or stubbornness of not
o o por cabezonería de no llevarle la
contradicting
contraria a
Dallas that I can't think of anything else
Dallas que no se me ocurre más nada de
really and well the last song of the
verdad y bueno el último tema de la
night the last song of the
noche el último tema de la
night that a lot of people are sending me you
noche que me lo estáis mandando mucha
're sending me this a lot I
gente me estáis mandando esto mucho
'll have to investigate a little more I don't know
tendré que investigar un poco más no sé
if I should address it Oh I don't know if I should address this
si tratarlo Ah lo no sé si tratar este
topic or leave it for the main channel
tema o dejarlo para el canal
Ah I don't know if I should address it in the main one
Ah no sé si tratarlo en el principal
well exposed because I have more
bien expuesto porque tengo más
information that they start sending me
información que se ponen a a mandarme
privately okay let's see Well let's
privado vale a ver Bueno vamos a
talk about it a little bit and that's it It
hablarlo por encima un poco y ya vale
turns out that you remember tp
Resulta ser que os acordáis de tp
resurrection which was a guy who accused
resurrection que era un tío que acusaba
Dallas of scamming for being deos well he
de estafa a Dallas por estar deos pues
's being canceled a lot in his
está siendo canceladísimo en todo su
environment and by a lot of youtubers for
entorno y por un montón de youtubers por
scamming okay in two videos that
estafar vale en dos vídeos que ha hecho
Marciano blog made one of  A few days ago and another one
Marciano blog uno de Hace unos días y
from A few hours ago exposes tp
otro de Hace unas horas expone a tp
resurrection apparently tp resurrection
resurrection al parecer tp resurrection
was promoting a
estuvo promocionando un negocio
pyramid business that ended up being a scam
piramidal que terminó siendo una estafa
to its followers here is a screenshot of a
a sus seguidores acá una captura de un
follower who invested money and then did not
seguidor que invirtió dinero y luego no
receive the
recibió la rentabilidad
expected return it is to ask how the
esperada es para preguntar cómo va el
investment process is going And if I managed to generate
proceso de inversión Y si logré generar
profitability Welcome to our
rentabilidad Bienvenido a nuestro
investment program I am Harry and
programa de inversión yo soy Harry y el
today I will be informing you about
día de hoy te estaré informando sobre
everything we can do for
todo lo que podemos hacer por
you or so apparently there is
ti o sea por lo visto hay
one
una
if I
si os
tell you if I tell you the message that just
digo si os digo el mensaje que me acaba
arrived
llegar
an if I tell you the message that just
an si os digo el mensaje que me acaba de
arrived just broke my ass the
llegar me acaba de romper el culo el
message that just
mensaje que me acaba de
arrived
llegar
Thank goodness I'm with the
Menos mal que estoy con el filtro
crab filter eh I mean if this doesn't end up being
cangrejo eh o sea si esto no llega a ser
with the
con el filtro
crab filter if this doesn't end up being done with the crab
cangrejo si esto no llega a hacer con el
filter [ __ ] [ __ ] Wait Wait I have to
filtro
answer
contestarle a
this
esto
seriously seriously No no I'm joking
en serio en serio No no es coña
eh I mean no I'm not going to tell the
eh o sea no no lo voy a contar el
message because it's a private message
mensaje porque es un mensaje privado
and and they have told me can I say what you
y y me han le he dicho puedo decir lo
just told me because it's  that I just
que me acabas de decir porque es que se
broke my
me acaba de romper el
ass I just broke my ass what
culo se me acaba de romper el culo lo
you can least
que menos os
imagine what you can least
imaginéis lo que menos os
imagine what you can least imagine it's
imaginéis lo que menos os imaginéis va
related to the topic we were
relacionado sobre el tema que estábamos
talking about all night
hablando durante toda la noche
okay so one of the
vale o sea me ha escrito uno de los
protagonists of the night wrote to me that's the only thing I
protagonistas de la noche es lo único
can tell you but I'm not going to
que os puedo decir pero no os voy a
tell you the content obviously
decir el contenido evidentemente
let's not even tell you who it is
vamos ni os voy a decir qué persona es
but the message is very strong
pero es muy fuerte el
saa it's a message that if
mensaje saa es que es un mensaje que si
this comes true it's going to break the
esto se cumple va a romper
internet I just fell dead
internet Me acabo de quedar muert
sim
simo
wait for that That one
espera esa Esa
forgive me eh it's that I
esa perdonadme eh que es que esto tengo
have to
que
clarify this it's that you ca
aclararlo
n't
es que no os podéis
imagine the magnitude of the
imaginar de la magnitud que es la
conversation I'm
conversación que estoy
having it's that I can't
teniendo es que no me lo puedo
believe it
creer
obviously I'm not going to tell anything
evidentemente no voy a contar nada
obviously I'm not going to tell anything eh I
evidentemente no voy a contar nada eh No
'm not creating H because it's that I can't I'm
estoy creando H porque es que no lo
not going to
puedo no lo voy a
tell it I'm trying to assimilate what they've
contar estoy intentando asimilar lo que
written to me and I'm asking a
me han escrito y le estoy haciendo un
couple of questions to that person who
par de preguntas a esa persona que me ha
wrote to me it's not a joke
escrito no es coña
eh It's not a
eh No es
joke
coña
So why are you increasing the H I'm not
Entonces por qué aumentas el H no estoy
no  I'm increasing anything I
no estoy aumentando ningún hte os lo
promise you that I'm not increasing anything I
prometo que no estoy aumentando ningún
promise you that I'm
hte os prometo que estoy
freaking out Thank goodness he caught me with
flipando Menos mal que me ha cogido con
the [ __ ]
el [__]
filter you always do the same thing dude no I
filtro siempre haces lo mismo tío no no
can't let's see it's not that I'm
puedo a ver que no es que yo lo esté
doing it that it's that no because I can't
haciendo que es que no porque no puedo
tell you something it's that but it's not that I can't
deciros algo es que pero es que no es
tell you it's that I couldn't not have
que no pueda deciros es que no podría no
reacted to what just
haber reaccionado a esto que me acaba de
happened to me I mean it happened to me
pasar o sea es que me ha pasado en
live maybe the person Even if he
directo a lo mejor la persona Incluso si
's watching me it bothers him
me está viendo le molesta
Fran What are you doing dude Fran I thought you
Fran Qué haces cabrón Fran creía que
were
estabas en
live of course I did it dude
directo claro le he hecho buah
guys I [ __ ] on my [ __ ] life
chavales me cago en mi [__] vida
I [ __ ] on my [ __ ]
me cago en mi [__]
life I can't assimilate what just
vida no pu no puedo asimilar lo que
happened a dick a
pasar una
dick
[__]
quickly I can't I can't
rápido
believe it dude I can't
puedo no puedo creérmelo tío no puedo
believe it but give us clues negative or
creérmelo pero danos pistas negativo o
positive well I asked
positivo pues le he hecho una pregunta a
this person a question I asked him a question not
esta persona le he hecho una pregunta no
to tell you the answer because I would
para contaros la respuesta porque yo lo
if they talk to me in private I don't tell what they
si me hablan en privado yo no cuento lo
tell me in private it's never worth it the
que me dicen en privado nunca vale lo
only thing I can tell you is that he's one
único que os puedo decir es que es uno
of the  protagonists of the
de los protagonistas de la
night I was watching the live
noche estaba viendo el directo
and he gave me a
y me ha dado un
headline that could blow up the
titular que puedes puede estallar
internet and then as I didn't know if I
internet y entonces como yo no sabía si
was understanding it
lo estaba si lo estaba entendiendo
correctly as I didn't know if I was
bien como yo no sabía si lo estaba
understanding it correctly I asked him a
entendiendo bien le he hecho una
question to see if his messages were going
pregunta para ver si lo tiros van por
where I think they were or
donde yo pienso o
not
no
but he already left me on read from 3
pero ya me ha dejado en visto de hace 3
minutes ago but this guy this guy can't
minutos pero este tío este tío no me
send me this message and leave me
puede mandar Este mensaje y dejarme
like that no no I asked him go Alex I
así no no le he preguntado vay Alex le
asked him and I said do you mind if I
he preguntado y le he dicho te importa
say the message you
que diga en directo el mensaje que me
just sent me live and he'd rather not he'd
acabas de mandar y prefiere que no
rather not
prefiere que no
but wait I'm going to send him a message I
pero espérate le voy a mandar un mensaje
'm going to put him down you [ __ ] you don't leave me like this
le voy a poner cabrón no me dejas
[ __ ] It's a good thing he caught me
así cabrón Menos mal que me ha cogido
with a filter eh I mean no no I'm not going to
con filtro eh o sea no no yo no voy a
say anything I'm not going to say anything but
decir nada yo no voy a decir nada pero
[ __ ] it's that I couldn't help it
[__] es que no he podido evitar
forgive me for cutting the extract
perdonadme que haya cortado el extracto
eh I couldn't help it It's that I didn't expect it I mean it's that I didn't expect it I did
eh es que no lo he podido evitar Es que
n't expect it I mean I'm freaking out I'm freaking out did you know they
es que no me lo esperaba o sea es que no
closed
flipo flipo supiste que le cerraron
twitch Roma  Gallardo no but it will have been
twich Roma Gallardo no pero habrá sido
today no because I was with Roma yesterday
hoy no porque yo estado con Roma ayer
here I was with Roma today
aquí yo estuve con Roma hoy
here [ __ ] Fran just gave me an
aquí [__] Fran me acaba de dar una
exclusive
exclusiva
uncle
tío
Franco this just gave me I'm sitting here
Franco esta me acaba de Yo aquí estoy
dressed as a crab
sentado vestido de cangrejo me están
these exclusives are coming in like crazy
llegando las exclusivas que te cagas
okay family let's
vale familia a
see I just got an
ver me acaba de llegar una
exclusive I just got an
exclusiva me acaba de llegar una
exclusive and I can tell you it it's not it's not
exclusiva y puedo contarlo no es no es
the same
la misma
exclusive that I cut off the
exclusiva por la que he cortado el
previous stranger for okay I mean what
extrao anterior vale o sea lo que ha
happened a few seconds ago is
pasado hace unos segundos no tiene
inexplicable I just broke my
explicación se me acaba de romper el
ass okay we were talking about
culo vale nosotros estábamos hablando de
something and one of the main characters
un tema y uno de los protagonistas me ha
wrote to me to tell me something something very
escrito para decirme algo algo muy
strong but I can't say it I'm going to
fuerte pero no lo puedo decir voy a
try to talk to him privately okay
intentar hablar con él por privado vale
at least so he doesn't leave me like this
por lo menos para que no me deje así
because the truth is I'm freaking out
porque la verdad es que estoy flipando
okay but while I was trying to
vale pero mientras que estaba intentando
process this other
asimilar esto otro
uh while I was trying to
eh mientras que estaba yo intentando
process the other message that they
asimilar el otro mensaje que me han
sent me I just got
mandado me acaba de llegar por privado
another
otra
exclusive privately
exclusiva
directly
directamente
directly I just got the
directamente me acaba de llegar la
next
siguiente
exclusive pay attention
exclusiva atentos
okay I
vale
'm going to
voy a volver a
read it again I'm going to
leerlo voy a volver a
read it again Fran
leerlo Fran
cua Frank
cua Frank
cua sent me the next message you
cua me manda el siguiente mensaje te
deserve to be left hanging Javi  Look
mereces que te dejen colgado Javi Mira
how you have
cómo nos tienes a
us already but I don't want to leave you
nosotros ya pero yo no quiero dejaros
hanging in fact what I'm
colgados de hecho lo que yo estoy
doing forgive me what I'm
haciendo perdonadme lo que yo estoy
doing with the other message that I
haciendo con el otro mensaje que me ha
got is
llegado es
trying to find out why they sent me is It's that I ca
intentar saber porque me han puesto es
n't tell you because of course
Es que no os puedo decir porque claro
explaining what they sent me I would
explicaros lo que me han mandado os
tell you Who is the person who
contaría Quién es la persona que me ha
wrote to me okay a person wrote to me who
escrito vale me ha escrito una persona
with well it's that I can't tell you I'm
que con bueno es que no puedo deciros
going to tell you this exclusive and the other one I'll
voy a contaros esta exclusiva y la otra
see if it comes out if it doesn't And if it could be
ya veo si sale si no sale Y si puede ser
that it comes out Here is what I told
que salga Aquí es lo que le he dicho a
that person uh I told him Hey what do I have to
esa persona eh le he dicho Oye qué tengo
do so that what is it for that
que hacer para que que es para que esa
exclusive to come out Here
exclusiva salga Aquí
[Music]
[Música]
and Fran cua just sent me a
e Fran cua me acaba de mandar un
WhatsApp well do it on silent
WhatsApp pues hazlo en silencio
Jai let's see if he has marked me on
Jai a ver voy a ver si me ha marcado el
read let's say to the other person that I
visto le le a la otra persona que con la
was talking to I marked him [ __ ]
que estaba hablando le he puesto cabrón
don't leave me like that
no me dejes así
Hahaha But no they don't leave me seen or
Jajaja Pero no ya no me dejan visto ni
anything I think that tomorrow he will
nada Creo que mañana se habrá
regret having sent me that
arrepentido de haber me mandar ese
message but well it's okay don't
mensaje pero bueno no pasa nada que no
worry because I
se preocupe porque yo los mensajes
never
privados nunca los
say private messages Fran  cua just sent me a
digo Fran cua me acaba de mandar un
WhatsApp Thank you very much
WhatsApp Muchas gracias
Román Fran cuesta just sent me a
Román Fran cuesta me acaba de mandar un
WhatsApp and Fran s told me that I can
WhatsApp y Fran s me ha dicho que puedo
read his WhatsApp I'll read it to you I'll
leer su WhatsApp os lo leo os lo
read it to you I'll read it to you
leo os lo
okay I'll
leo vale os lo
read it to you Fran
leo Fran
cua
cua me
tells me I
dice
confirm that
confirmo que
Dallas is coming to support the work at the
Dallas viene a apoyar el trabajo en el
sanctuary in
santuario en
September there
septiembre
will be
habrá
Franeta and Dallas in
de franeta y Dallas en
September at the
septiembre en el
sanctuary Fran cua just sent it to me
santuario me lo acaba de mandar Fran cua
exclusively for all of
en exclusiva para todos
you
ustedes
buah Hey, well I'm really happy I'm
buah Oye pues me alegro muchísimo me
really happy man I'm
alegro muchísimo tío me alegro
really, really happy some really
muchisísimo muchisísimo saldrá contenido
cool content will come out of it some really
muy guapo de ahí saldrá contenido
cool content will come out of it really cool the truth is
guapísimo de ahí chulísimo la verdad
really cool I don't see the tongs applaud no
chulísimo no veo las tenazas aplaudir no
but I'm not following the one who's applauding
pero yo no sigo el que aplaudido están
the people are applauding over here okay Wow no
aplaudiendo la peña por aquí vale Wow no
I didn't expect it to be so so
me no me esperaba que fuera tan tan
fast I didn't expect it to be
rápido No me esperaba que fuese
already
ya
brutal brutal brutal I'm a little in
brutal brutal brutal estoy un poco en
shock with the other topic eh I'm a little
shock con el otro tema eh estoy un poco
in shock with the other topic I want to feel
en shock con el otro tema quiero sentir
your body j
tu cuerpo j
my no the other topic is that I can't
mi no el otro tema es que no lo puedo
tell it But well, what do I know you can
contar Pero bueno yo que sé podéis
imagine  whatever you want you can
imaginaros lo que queráis podéis
imagine whatever you
imaginaros lo que
want the other person who
queráis la la otra persona que me ha
wrote to me has left me broken Because
escrito me ha dejado el culo roto Porque
also the message that
además es que el mensaje que me ha dado
the other person gave me
la otra persona
uh the message that the other person gave us the
eh el mensaje que nos ha dado la otra el
message that the other person gave me I do
mensaje que me ha dado la otra
n't know if it was
persona no sé si ha
focused on one side or focused on the
sido enfocado a un lado o enfocado a
other
otro
side
lado me
you know what I mean
entendéis
But well that's it if they want to tell me
Pero bueno ya está si me lo quiere decir
because they tell me that's it I imagine that
porque me lo diga ya está me imagino que
Ah I imagine that
Ah me imagino que
Ah how angry it makes me many times when they
Ah qué rabia me da muchas veces que me
tell me these things
cuenten estas cosas
man it does
tío
n't make me
no me da
angry because it's very
rabia porque es muy
strong but of course it makes me angry now
fuerte pero claro me da rabia ahora
having to keep quiet because I don't like to
tener que callel porque no me gusta
tell the I don't like to tell the things
contar las no me gusta contar las cosas
that they tell me in private lest they
que me dicen en privado a no s que de
suddenly betray me and say Hey well you
repente me traicionen y diga Oye pues tú
told me this you understand but I have to
me dijiste esto me entiendes pero tengo
tell you that I have to I have to tell you that that's that I do
que deciros
n't know how to tell you this without
que es que no sé cómo deciros esto sin
betraying the person who wrote to me I
delatar a la persona que me ha escrito
have to tell you that while I
tengo que deciros que mientras que
was in the other extract that I just
estaba en el otro extracto que acabo de
cut a
cortar me ha escrito de repente una
person who is the
persona
protagonist of the night or rather the
protagonista de la noche o sea
protagonist of one of  the topics we
protagonista de uno de los temas que
were discussing and it's not Rubiales It's
estábamos tratando y no es rubiales Es
the only thing I can tell you and he
lo único que os puedo decir y me ha
told me something that I think is
dicho algo que yo creo
clear what happens is that I didn't
claro lo que pasa es que yo no lo he
understand it Maybe I'm
entendido A lo mejor lo estoy
understanding it wrong eh and I'll come back crazier
entendiendo mal eh y volveré más loco
than ever
que nunca
Javi I'll come back crazier than ever let's see It's that I ca
Javi volveré más loco que nunca a ver Es
n't tell you the truth I can't
que no puedo deciros lo de verdad no
say the truth it's not my it's not
puedo decirlo de verdad no es mi no es
My way of doing it's not My way of doing it What
Mi proceder no es Mi proceder Lo que
happens is forgive me because it's that when I
pasa que perdonarme porque es que cuando
saw that message well I couldn't
he visto ese mensaje pues no he podido
help it because it's very strong damn I don't know
evitar porque es muy fuerte [__] No sé
how he thought it's I don't know I don't
cómo se la ha pasado por la es que no sé
know how he thought of
por la no sé cómo se la ha pasado por la
sending me a message damn and leaving me like that no no it
cabeza mandarme mensaje [__] y dejarme
's Dalas it's not good that's it
así no no es Dalas no es bueno ya está
stop asking me because if not but
dejarme de preguntar porque si no pero
no oh I have to watch something from
no ay tengo que ver una cosa de
Gref I have to watch something from Gref
gref tengo que ver una cosa de gref
now that you've reminded me man I
ahora que me la habéis recordado tío
have to watch something from Gref and I'm
tengo que ver una cosa de gre y ya me
leaving eh what I want to record newscasts if
voy eh que Quiero grabar noticieros si
each one gives super chat 10 I'll tell it no
cada uno da super chat 10 lo cuento no
man
tío
eh no no no I can't tell it it's not a problem no no problem
eh no no no no puedo contarlo no pasa
Look I can't
nada no no pasa nada Mira no puedo
tell it first of all
contarlo en primer lugar
Because because I do
Porque porque yo las com ases privadas
n't tell anyone about private things And secondly
no se las cuento a nadie Y en segundo
because I would like
lugar porque me gustaría
that I would like if there is something to tell that it would be
que me gustaría si hay algo que contar
told So if we start with
que se contara Entonces si empezamos con
the Nonsense Well maybe it won't be
las Tonterías Pues a lo mejor no se
told okay That's it let's leave it there
cuenta vale Ya está vamos a dejarlo ahí
eh they sent me something I think it was
eh me mandaron algo creo que fue el
Will's theater Will's theater sent me something today
Will el teatro de Will me mandó algo hoy
look here we have it so I could watch it
mira aquí lo tenemos para que lo viera
live but I don't know exactly what it's about they
en directo pero no sé exactamente De qué
also just sent me something
a también me acaban de mandar una cosa
from nimu the night gets longer The
de nimu se alarga la noche Se alarga la
night gets longer what is it he says This is gref
noche qué es lo que es dice Este es gref
a streamer youtuber with so much money
un streamer youtuber con tanto dinero
that apparently he doesn't give a damn about the rules
que al parecer se la pelan las reglas
here he tells the fantastic story of
aquí narra la fantástica historia de
how he ignores the rules of the
cómo se pasa por el [__] las normas del
concert he went to and then treats
concierto al que fue y después trata
the woman who tries to
como una loca a la mujer que intenta
recriminate him like crazy okay obviously this was
recriminar selo vale obviamente esta era
much better than A3 I happened to
muchísimo mejor que A3 a mí me tocó
be in A3 in seat number 20 in
estar en A3 en la butaca número 20 de la
row his [ __ ] mother but I noticed How to
fila su [__] madre pero yo noté Cómo
say it that it wasn't at all difficult to go
decirlo que no era del todo difícil ir
here because there were simply chairs and
aquí porque simplemente había sillas y
because I wanted Ar  and sing what I did
porque yo quería Ar y cantar qué hice
stealthily I was taking little steps until
disimuladamente fui dando pasitos hasta
suddenly I was in a1
que de repente yo estaba en a1
Ah for the face and the truth is that I didn't give a
Ah por la cara y la verdad es que me la
damn and I enjoyed the
peló una auténtica barbaridad y disfruté
concert a
del concierto a un
step away yes I admit it I wasn't in my
paso sí lo reconozco No estuve en mi
seat I wasn't in my seat because I
asiento No estuve en mi asiento porque
had gone to Miami to see Carol G and I
había ido a Miami para ver a Carol G y
was going to fight to be very close Ah there was
iba a luchar por estar muy cerca Ah hubo
a moment when here a girl
un momento en el que aquí una chica me
said to me Hey would you mind going back to your
dijo Oye te importaría volver a tu
chair my response was what to which she
silla mi respuesta fue qué a lo que ella
replied your chair and
contestó tu silla y
I what chair has
yo qué silla se ha
disappeared I turned around and we
perdido me di la vuelta y
continued You think dude that you can do it
seguimos Tú te crees tío que puedas
but it's not doing it anymore no yes no it's not doing it anymore
hacer pero ya no es hacerlo no si
Well another day
no ya no es hacerlo Pues otro día más
that he is not residing in Andorra
que no está residiendo en andorra
tax agency warms up that ent but
agencia tributaria calienta que ent pero
dude it's not that you do it but that you take it
tío ya no es que lo hagas sino que cojas
and tell it
y lo cuentes
proudly this kid dude this kid is
orgulloso este chaval tío este chico es
for real okay obviously he is this kid I mean
de verdad vale obviamente es este chico
But how do you tell it and tell it
o sea Pero cómo lo cuentas y lo cuentas
there like a
ahí como una
joke elite moves
gracia movidas de la élite movidas de la
elite moves
élite
it's that it's not that you do it no because
es que ya no es que lo hagas no porque
in the end what do I know  imagine no who
al final yo que sé imagínate no quién
has changed us who has changed our
nos ha cambiado de quién nos ha cambiado
seats in the cinema When they had the
de silla en el cine Cuando ha tenido la
chance no but there I imagine that the
ocasión no pero ahí me imagino que las
chairs would have been quite numbered I don't think there
sillas estarían bastante enumeradas No
were free seats and less
creo que hubiese sitios libres y menos
in that area but that you take it and tell it and
en esa zona pero que cojas y lo cuente y
that you have fooled around with the girl who
que le has vacilado a la chica que te lo
reproaches you this guy really doesn't last
recrimina este chico de verdad no dura
eh He doesn't mature
eh No madura
eh I have to see another clip of nimu but it's that I
eh tengo que ver otro clip de nimu pero
promise you that he has left my
es que os lo prometo que me ha dejado el
ass broken that
culo rotísimo ese
message is that I'm even checking
mensaje es que estoy incluso comprobando
that let's go that the person who
que vamos que la persona que me ha
sent me that message is really him And yes yes yes it is
mandado ese mensaje es él realmente Y sí
him it's that I curse my
él es que me cago en mi
life how can you send me This and
vida cómo me puedes mandar Este y
stay
quedarte
like that
así
wow
wow
wow the things that don't happen here don't happen
wow las cosas que no pasan aquí no pasan
guys let's see luare just sent me
chavales a ver me acaba de mandar luare
I'm here trying to
yo aquí intentando
leave I'm here trying to leave and luares just
irme yo aquí intentando irme y luares me
sent me some [ __ ] I understand that
acaba de mandar una movida entiendo que
this thing that luare sends me I mean I
esta movida que me manda luare o sea
'm seeing that it's a live stream from nimu and I
estoy viendo que es un directo de nimu y
understand that when luar is
entiendo que cuando luar me está
sending me this [ __ ] it's because nimus is
mandando esta movida es porque nimus ya
no longer in  Andorra
no está en andorra
no
no
some of you are right but no I
algunos estáis acertando pero no yo
have my way of working okay
tengo mi forma de trabajar vale
And I have my way of working
Y yo tengo mi forma de trabajar
and it is different okay So do
y es de otra manera vale Así que no me
n't worry as soon as I can
no os preocupéis que en cuanto yo pueda
and things can be done well and if I
y se puedan hacer las cosas bien y si
can get the information out well You'll have it
puedo sacar la información bien lo Vais
here
a tener aquí
okay I could tell it would be a bomb
vale podría contarlo sería una bomba
but like this it's not worth it I mean I prefer that
pero así no vale o sea que prefiero que
the person comes to tell it I'm not telling you
venga la persona a contarlo no te digo
the I'm not going to tell you the lie let's see I understand
la no te voy a decir la mentira a ver
that Nimu I understand that
entiendo que nimu entiendo que
Nimu is no longer in Andorra No if he is
nimu ya no está en andorra No si está
doing these live shows doing a
haciendo estos directos haciendo un
live show in Andorra with my friend Delox and
directo en andorra con mi amigo delox y
his girlfriend mind you his friend Delox but well
su novia ojo su amigo delox pero bueno
Delox what a stab you just gave me eh
delox vaya puñal que me acabas de dar eh
being friends of my enemies friends
siendo amigos de mis enemigos amigos
Javi It's that I can't take you seriously
Javi Es que no puedo tomarte en serio
with that filter well I hope that when or if it's
con ese filtro pues espero que cuando o
true I hope that if that happens I
sea de verdad espero que si pasa eso
hope that if that happens he catches me with a
espero que si eso ocurre me coja con
different look I mean you can't
otro look o sea es que no podéis
imagine the physical appearance that I
imaginaros la apariencia física que
have right now in fact let's see I'm
tengo en estos momentos de hecho a ver
going to look at the camera Because look
me voy a mirar en la cámara Porque mira
something happened to me this afternoon let's
me ha pasado algo esta tarde a
see it seems that now  that I just
ver parece que ahora que me acabo de
took the medication it has lowered a
tomar la medicación se ha rebajado un
little but not so much it's that
poco pero no tanto es
right now I don't know if I look like and I
que ahora mismo no sé si parezco y yo
Juan or set tangana I don't know right now what I
Juan o set tangana no sé ahora mismo lo
look like But before I was doing a
que parezco Pero antes estaba haciendo
live with Marina and when I started to do it
directo con Marina y cuando he empezado
live Well the truth is that I
a ha directo Pues la verdad es que
was fine I had an appearance well
estaba bien tenía una apariencia bueno
within the baldness that they gave me
dentro del pelado que me han hecho pues
more or less acceptable but when I
más o menos aceptable pero cuando he
finished the live with Marina I took the
terminado el directo con Marina he
dog down and when I saw myself in
bajado al perro y cuando me he visto en
the elevator in the mirror I said what
el ascensor en el espejo he dicho qué
what guy my whole head had swollen up
qué tío se me había inflado toda la
the whole top of my
cabeza toda la parte de arriba de la
head here around the 100 around
cabeza aquí por la parte de la 100 por
the eyebrow super swollen
la parte de la ceja super hinchad simo
man suddenly while I was
tío de repente en el tiempo que estaba
doing the live man it was brutal and
haciendo el directo tío ha sido brutal y
this happens and this happens in the middle of
pasa esto y pasa esto en plenos
Tri
Tri
no nothing nothing nothing everything correct All
no nada nada nada todo correcto Todo
good Don't be an [ __ ] You're welcome friends
bien No seas cabrón De nada amigos de
nothing friends the streamer who
nada amigos la streamer que
recently Okay Okay they
recientemente se enc Okay Okay me
signed me filmed my whole ass on full
firmaron me filmó todo el [__] en plena
screen friend seriously my ass is
pantalla amigo en serio tengo el culo
so so big so Magnate and so colossal
tan tan grande tan Magnate y tan colosal
so voluptuous so  voluminous so so you
tan voluptuoso tan voluminoso tan tan me
understand me so so giant
entendés tan tan gigante
eh Monumental titanic you understand me and I
eh Monumental titánico me entendés y yo
said friend What an ass I have on the
dije amigo Qué culo que tengo por el
other side why is there so much fuss over
otro lado porque hay tanto revuelo por
an ass is an ass is my ass it's
un culo es un culo es mi culo no pasa
okay but no it's not don't fudge the kid's not
nada pero no lo no me lo funen al pibe
fudge the kid's if after
no me lo funen al pibe si yo después de
that I recorded him or him too but It's
eso yo le grabé el or él también per No
okay I laugh at it and nothing an
pasa nada yo me lo tomo a risa y nada un
anecdotal rcan the balls ent in
anecdótico rcan los huevos ent entre
parentheses like me saying What's up the
paréntesis como yo diciendo Qué pasa el
clip is this one no Ah they scratch their balls
clip es este no Ah se rascan los huevos
Ah about the police where we talked about it about
Ah lo de la policía dónde lo comentamos
the police we talked about this in
lo de la policía esto lo comentamos en
one of the last newscasts I think but
uno de los últimos noticieros creo pero
for good reasons over there in Latin America they
por buenas razones allá en Latinoamérica
also scratch their balls they're
también se rascan los huevos muy
not very different but over there they scratch their
diferentes no son pero allá se rascan
balls while they steal from you and
los huevos mientras te caban choreando y
brunen for example once they robbed his
brunen por ejemplo una vez le robaron en
car guy they broke the window of the
el auto tipo le rompieron el vidrio del
car and robbed him How crazy a crazy
auto y le robaron Qué locura una locura
live on top of that What do you say Yes it's all
en directo encima Qué dices Sí está todo
recorded I'll show it to you later if you want
grabado después te lo muestro si quieres
And what surprises you well basically That's
Y de qué te sorpr bueno básicamente Ese
the clip What's happening people the
es el clip Qué pasa la gente los
Andorran police got angry with me
policías de andorra Se enojaron conmigo
or rather according to delo they published it in
o sea según según delo lo publicaron en
a group of Andorran police and they
un grupo de policías andorranos y
were all outraged a lady went
estaban todos indignados fue una señora
to curse delox in a private message
a [__] a puteadas a delox al privado
telling him that he was disrespectful but
diciéndole que que falta de respeto pero
if we're telling them that Andorra is so
si les estamos diciendo que es tan
safe that the police
seguro andorra que que los policías
can scratch their balls dude in
pueden des rascarse las bolas boludo en
10 seconds 30 seconds there's not even one
10 segundos 30 segundos no hay ni un
message and that depresses me in a
mensaje y eso a mí me me deprime de una
way I
manera
want to be Stream if there are no
manero quiero siendo Stream si no ha
videos on YouTube and I like Stream is
videos en YouTube y me gusta Stream es
like your comments on the other hand
gust sus comentarios por otro lado la
misinformation is the bread of every day there is no
desinformación es el pan de cada día no
one
hay nadie
who doubts for a second the misinformation
que dude ni un segundo la desinformación
that is
que está
falling while I read comment how I want to
cayendo rato Leo comentari como quiero
forgive
perdonar
00 and min times it's
a00 y min veces es
like I usually
como soliendo
listen
escuche
can understand a little these things
se pueda entender un poco estas cosas
because the truth is that it is not ugly to
porque la verdad es que no está fea a
anyone guys and this scam scam
nadie chicos y esto de estafó estafó
scam is a misinterpretation and it is a
estafó es una malinterpretación y es una
resounding misinformation I do not scam
desinformación rotunda yo no estaf a
anyone I do not scam anyone with evidence
nadie no estaf a nadie con pruebas no
is not F to anyone is a  misinformation that
está F a nadie es una desinformación que
people said it like a
la gente la dijo como teléfono
game of telephone and when someone tries to
descompuesto y cuando alguien intenta
deny it they go and insult them Nobody can
desmentir van y lo insultan Nadie puede
say what are you saying because they
decir ch está qu estás diciendo porque
go and insult them it's like Man it's so
van y lo insultan es como Man está tan
fashionable to insult me ​​slander me and say things
de moda insultarme difarme y decir cosas
that are not true that everyone supports her it's a
que no son que todo el mundo la apoya es
joke it's a joke
una paja es una paja
eh it's like But well nothing I have faith
eh es como Pero bueno nada yo tengo fe
that after the podcast this situation
que después del podcast esta situación
will be
se va a
reversed Well both she and Delo
revertir Bueno tanto ella como delo
are convinced that after the
están convencidos de que después del
podcast this situation can be reversed
podcast se puede revertir esta situación
well what Nimu did wasn't that bad either let's
bueno tampoco fue tan malo lo que hizo
see well let's see there are people who have
nimu a ver bueno a ver hay gente que
done worse things
hecho cosas peores
no well let's see we would have to take
no bueno a ver tendríamos que hacer
stock Once the
balance Una vez que se estrene el
podcast is released which by the way
podcast que por cierto
delox will come when it has the teaser
delox va a venir cuando tenga el teaser
I think the teaser will be available
Yo creo que el teaser lo va a tener
after Ma I think I think eh I think I think they will
pasado Ma yo creo creo eh creo Creo que
have the teaser the day after tomorrow
el teaser lo tendrán pasado mañana
approximately I don't think they will
aproximadamente No creo que mañana lo
have it tomorrow from what I have spoken today with
tengan por lo que he hablado hoy con
Delox I don't think they will have it tomorrow I
delox no creo que lo tengan mañana yo
think they will have the teaser the day after
creo que el teaser lo van a tener pasado
tomorrow I think we will do it here okay the
mañana creo que lo aremos aquí vale el
taser we are going to release it here
taser lo vamos a estrenar aquí subirá
delox will upload and he is going to put the taser here
delox y nos lo va a poner aquí el taser
exclusively, which is no small thing, and
en exclusiva que no es poca cosa que
apparently nimu has approved
además por lo visto nimu ha aprobado que
the teaser. Look, no, nimu has approved
el teaser fijaros no nimu ha aprobado
that the teer be put here, that the taser be
que el teer se ponga aquí que el taser
put here on the canijo, okay,
se ponga aquí en el canijo vale en
exclusively, and I think the date of the
exclusiva y creo que la fecha del
podcast will be Sunday, that is what would make
podcast será el domingo es lo que a mí
sense to me. No, deos has not told me that,
me cuadraría no no me lo ha dicho deos
eh, but it is what would make sense to me, that it is on
eh pero es lo que a mí me cuadraría que
a Sunday, not a Friday or a
sea un domingo no un viernes ni un
Saturday, the
sábado la
truth is, I think that I think that the teaser
verdad yo creo que yo creo que el teaser
tomorrow, which is Thursday, well, I think that the
mañana que es jueves pues yo creo que el
teaser will make me one of those who do a
teaser me hará de los que hagamos un
live broadcast on Friday to put the teaser
directo el viernes para poner el teaser
and and does that mean that on Sunday,
y y querrá decir eso que el domingo
that on Sunday the podcast will premiere, okay,
e que el domingo se se estrenará el
I'm freaking out, well, see, I'm not
es que estoy flipando bueno ver tampoco
freaking out that much, I'm freaking out, but
estoy flipando tanto estoy flipando pero
no, not because one person spoke to me
no no porque me haya hablado una persona
because at this point I'm not freaking out about
porque yo no me flipo a estas alturas de
certain people
que ciertas personas me
talking to me, I think I'm freaking out based on the
hablen yo creo yo estoy flipando por la
information that I have handled right now,
información que he manejado ahora mismo
okay, let's see, I'm going to say something that
vale a ver voy a decir una cosa que me
delox told me, which I understand is not  It will
dijo delox que entiendo que esto no le
bother me to say this but delox told me I
molestará que lo diga pero delox me dijo
just saw the
Acabo de ver el podcast de
nimu podcast it's in my top one and the ending is the
nimu está en mi top un y el final es la
most thing you've ever seen
cosa más que hayas visto
I think it's going to be a battle
nunca yo creo que va a ser una batalla
of headlines I think it's going to be a
de titulares yo creo que va a ser una
brutal battle of headlines I have faith that
batalla de titulares brutal tengo fe que
after the podcast this situation of
después del podcast esta situación de
that scammer and such after they
que estafadora y tal después de que lo
see it they will realize things and nothing They
vean sean dar cuenta de las cosas y nada
will stop a little with the scammer and
Van a parar un poco con la estafadora y
saying that [ __ ] that is not true I
de decir esa [__] que no es cierto
really have not done anything worse than
realmente no he hecho nada peor que
other people who have done things a thousand
otras personas que han hecho cosas mil
times worse But you don't make videos
veces peores Pero os no les hacen videos
because making videos of those people doesn't
porque hacerle videos a esas personas no
give them views if there is encouragement in the title encouragement the [ __ ] is going to get
les da visitas si hay nimo en el título
views that's why it
nimo la [__] n va a dar visitas por eso
seems like I'm repica But it's not like that and it's annoying it's
parece que estoy repica Pero no es así y
annoying because it's that
da bronca da bronca porque es esa
shitty conception that I
concepción de [__] de que de que yo
am controversial all day long and no no no it's not like that it's that
estoy polémica todo el día y no no no es
if V you look for controversy all
así es que si V buscas n polémica todos
the gossip channels rejoice over my
los canales de salseo se regocijan en mi
corpse like whes is
cadáver como whes es
like that which podcast so as not to lose it I went to
así cuál podcast para no perderlo fui
Andorra exclusively to do a
andorra exclusivamente para hacer un
podcast in person goes  to come out he had
podcast en persona va a salir había
confirmed the date he said he had a
confirmado la fecha de dijo que tenía
date for the taser well the podcast is going to come out in
fecha para el taser bueno va a salir en
September But it's going to come out at the
septiembre el podcast Pero va a salir en
beginning of September in less than a
inicio de septiembre en menos de una
week so you have an idea in less
semana para que tengan una idea en menos
Yes let's see I'm telling you it's what I
Sí vamos a ver te lo digo es que es lo
'm telling you today deos told me
que os estoy diciendo hoy deos me dijo
that he didn't have the teaser I imagine that
que el teaser no lo tenía me imagino que
tomorrow
mañana
either I imagine that on Friday
tampoco me imagino que el viernes el
Friday they will have the teaser and that's what I'm
viernes tendrán el teaser y es lo que te
telling you In other words the podcast is not going to be broadcast on the
digo O sea no se va a emitir el podcast
first nor the second nor the 3rd
el día un ni el día dos ni el día 3
Friday Saturday no the TR the TR Yes on
viernes sábado no el TR el TR Sí el
Sunday I understand that it will premiere on
domingo yo entiendo que se estrenará el
Sunday I think the podcast is going to come
domingo yo creo que el podcast va a
out on the 3rd Sunday it makes sense
salir el día 3 el domingo tiene lógica
that they premiere on a Sunday it's always
que se estren un domingo siempre es
Sunday it's not always Sunday in the
domingo no siempre es domingo por la
afternoon of a week the podcast is going to come out
tarde de una semana va a salir el
and it's going to come out on the channel without
podcast y va a salir en el canal sin
fear of success podcast this that made me
miedo al éxito podcast este que me hizo
was the first person who gave me a
fue la primer persona que me dio un
space and an opportunity to
espacio y un oportunidad para
talk I've told you that you were here
hablar yo te he dicho que eras aquí
many times too what happens is that of
muchas veces también lo que pasa que
course maybe I was going to ask you
claro a lo mejor te iba a hacer
questions and issues that were going to make you
preguntas y cuestiones que te iban a
uncomfortable and no  would you like to answer I don't know
incomodar y no querrías responder no sé
if maybe there for whatever reason he was doing I do
si a lo mejor allí por lo que sea hacia
n't know the truth I mean maybe he
no sé la verdad O sea a lo mejor se
thought I was going to be aggressive or something I
pensaba que yo iba a ser agresivo o algo
think Dallas also suggested we
creo que Dallas también le le propuso
debate not live no because everyone
debatir no en directo no porque todos
had the opportunity to insult me
tuvieron oportunidad para insultarme
denigrate me criticize me
para denigrar para criticarme para
marginalize me to make me [ __ ] and
margin arme para hacerme [__] y
destroy me on the ground eh in an
destruirme en el suelo eh de manera
unjustified and disproportionate way but nobody
injustificada y desmedida pero nadie me
gave me the space to speak because giving me the
dio el espacio para habl porque darme el
space to speak implied being a
espacio para hablar implicaba ser un
simp or it implied whitewashing a
simp o implicaba blanquear a una
scammer or whatever when it never
estafadora o lo que sea cuando nunca se
went like that and it's infuriating it's the
fue así y da rabia da rabia la cultura
cancel culture in the sense that of
de la cancelación en el sentido de que
course canceling is totally allowed
claro Cancelar está totalmente permitido
insulting yar is totally
insultar yar está totalmente
allowed but of course when the person
permitido pero claro cuando la persona
tries to defend themselves from those lies no no no don't
intenta defenderse de esas mentiras no
let them speak cure them that
no no no la dejen hablar cúrenla que
acronym insulting and mistreating and
sigla insultando y maltratando y
destroying until they can't take it anymore
destruyendo hasta que no pueda más
canceling because the person doesn't have the
cancelación porque la persona no tiene
right to speak only
No tiene derecho a hablar solamente
the haters have the right to speak and
tiene derecho a hablar los haters y el
whoever defends the person is an
que defienda a la persona es un
s it's horrible it doesn't make a damn
s es horrible no tiene ni un maldito
sense if you have time  to write a
sentido si tenes tiempo para escribir un
hate comment because you don't have
comentario de hate porque no tenes
time to listen to the other version
tiempo para escuchar la otra versión
too then that's
también entonces es
it if you keep talking about it the haters
eso si sigues hablando de loo los haters
will have to release all the material they
tendrán que saque todo el material que
need let them do what they want I
necesiten que hagan lo que quieran yo no
'm not saying anything out of this world
estoy diciendo nada del otro mundo
videos throwing [ __ ] at me give views and give
videos tirándome [__] da visitas y da
acceptance
aceptación
if you throw it you are based today you
si vos le tir estás basado al día de hoy
are totally based That is the issue
estás totalmente basado Ese es el tema
I do not think it is by visit because of
yo no creo que sea por visita porque de
visit or not being against nim in favor
visita o no estar en contra nim al favor
I think that in
Yo creo que de
fact I think that in fact it would harm
hecho yo creo que de hecho perjudicaría
more I mean you would be more surprised if
más O sea os sorprendería más que de
suddenly you saw here on screen nim I have to
repente vierais aquí en pantalla nim
defend yourself imagine that I
tengo que defenderte imagínate que yo
upload a video I say I am in favor of encouragement
subo un vídeo digo Estoy a favor de nimo
in this I would create more but let's see if you have
en esto crearía más pero a ver si tú has
created things that are criticizable because in the
creado cosas que son criticables pues al
end It is
final Es
logical
lógico logi
that the contents that are made are
que que los contenidos que se hagan sean
more negative against you than
más negativos contra ti que que
positive then that social acceptance
positivos entonces esa aceptación social
visits Obviously the
visitas Obviamente que los canales de
salt channels suit them But what's up with me
sal les conviene Pero qué onda conmigo
What's up with me that I am praying this
Qué onda conmigo que estoy reciendo este
justified that I am being the
justificado que estoy siendo el plato de
first table dish of all these people who
primera mesa de toda esta gente que
want to see blood why do I have to
quiere ver sangre por qué tengo que
put up with this just for  the good of
aguantar esto solamente por el bien del
entertainment and giving money to people
entretenimiento y darle dinero a gente
with hate
con odio
Well I think it wasn't that bad what he did Cheer up I'm going
Pues yo creo que no ha sido tan malo lo
guys to record the news I'm
nimo me voy a ir chavales a grabar noti
going to go I feel like
voy a ir me encuentro con ganas de
recording two newscasts I'm still going to go and I'm going to
grabar dos noticieros todavía voy a ir y
record both the
voy a grabar el tanto el noti de
kids' news and the one
chavales como el
about both the kids' news and the one about the
de tanto el noti de chavales como el de
women Okay what do you think I'm a
señoras Vale qué os parece me queda un
little in shock eh I'm a little in
poco en shock eh Me queda un poco en
shock I can't I can't hide it but oh
shock no puedo no puedo disimularlo pero
well as for tp resurrection I'll do it
bueno lo de tp resurrection ya lo hago
tomorrow in a video but I'm a
mañana en un vídeo pero me he quedado un
little in shock I really can't
poco en shock de verdad no os puedo
deny it I'm going to try to clarify that I'll
negar voy a intentar aclarar eso voy a
see if by turning off the live I can
ver si apagando el directo consigo
clarify it
aclararlo
guys huge kiss huge kiss okay
chicos beso enorme beso enorme vale
see you tomorrow a huge kiss
mañana nos vemos un beso enorme
guys
chicos
i
i